nanodanger7: hello hello
Samitugames : heyhey
acheesedanish00: acheesedanish00 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months!
gazny: dam from 6k to 9k IG god
Bombapil0t: going for 10k
nanodanger7: nice haircut
ffthgezgxjkndd: 69k next
sampleaccount123: yo
markvlk: 1m2019.com
sapphiiree_: THE MYTH THE MAN THE LEGEND
acheesedanish00: 3 streams in 2 days
foxubu: o/ new chair
psychosocial1810: dont forget to follow https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz
acheesedanish00: dope hair cut
lightofhel1: yo
cl_anubis: cl_anubis subscribed at Tier 1.
nightknight0000: lmao
lightofhel1: tomorrow it was 6k...
Mac_33: I told my mom to follow George Hotz on Instagram.
Bombapil0t: lol
hatem_xh: hi george .. what keyboard u are using ?
gazny: Reading YT comments PogChamp
W1lkins: TriHard 7
twiggy_io: What up young blood.
markvlk: You got a new chair
perkofficial: Howdy
kanogger: howdy
foxubu: Asking about the keyboard == ban! 🛑
Bombapil0t: Kreygasm
W1lkins: who purchased you 3.5k followers Kappa
kanogger: gonna hit 10k today PogChamp
AideTechBot: follower wave
Sowlz: how come your chome looks so good :(
zacoaa: lol
psychosocial1810: dx racer lit bro 😂 👌 🔥
lightofhel1: its geohotz progression LUL
AideTechBot: Did u get a haircut
Dsplits: @georgehotz are you buying your followers?
alluxua: whoops, you got your hair cut
slimpimp007: new cut huh
serhejenos: hi
Samitugames : What are you working today?
dorkmo: haircutttt
alienware997: I‘m the guy with the „Better Installer“ Commment, and i said that you get a level 2 Subscription from me in your next Stream. Now i have to drive to my bank and pay money in thanks! @georgehotz
kljok: I bought the followers
Dsplits: why do you want followers?
twiggy_io: Can you go into how funding works for startups?
alluxua: I like the long hair better
nagimohsen: Would you say math is needed as much as college makes it seem in order to be a good programmer
the_sadanie: Is Comma AI still alive?
toolegit2quit_: Did you pay for college ?
lavastew: the hobo look fit you better
BradyLange: BradyLange subscribed with Twitch Prime.
kanogger: www.1m2019.com
dorkmo: the new cherry hibiscus pure leaf tea taskes like hawaiian punch
CaptainAshtar: hey..... my fav streamer is online
alxhotel: 1m2019.com doesn't work through https
tea_em_oh_six: post more on instagram
foxubu: You should lean your back to the chair. (Neck issues) :Z
acheesedanish00: subscribe if he is your favorite lol
hackyhacks: lol
JonThomasK: everyones a unicorn
Keyeh: SeemsGood
th3_maj0r: nice hair cut bro
CaptainAshtar: CaptainAshtar subscribed at Tier 1.
nagimohsen: Are you a beast in math
acheesedanish00: gotta go :/
acheesedanish00: bye
ikoakmaindehoas: how about docker build --no-cache ?
Keyeh: perl in 2019 LUL
serhejenos: Nice to see you streaming frequantly
foxxible: is c good to learn as a second language?
b_______________________b: jcgD
Samitugames : 1 2?
alluxua: Hi geohot, did you get a girlfriend? Is that hiking girl your girlfriend?
doctrinacuriosa: @georgehotz what's vector space
Hashcatcs: forth > C
nagimohsen: Someone ask him a math question cause I suck
b_______________________b: @foxxible what do you wanna do with c
m0etaz: Math Q: what's a fourier transform?
Mac_33: indefinite integral of e^3x-1
foxxible: game development mainly
cIvIcbooks: i think you need to force exec syntax with a RUN command
cIvIcbooks: with brackets
Yellow_turd: @georgehotz in your opinion what is the best app developement language. Don't know if you have ever looked into app development or not
JonThomasK: if the std deviation of a series is 1 and the average is 0.50 what is 3 sigma?
foxxible: @b_______________________b game development mainly
b_______________________b: @foxxible depends how much you wanna do with your games
tomastakk: @Yellow_turd such thing doesn't exist
LegoNigel: pip!
Yellow_turd: @tomastakk what do you mean by such a thing doesnt exist
b_______________________b: @foxxible unity uses simple c# scripting and unreal but c I find is for people wanting to engineer games not just make games
Hashcatcs: @georgehotz will you ever do a video on reverse oriented programming ?
Airfrischung: whats 3 * 17?
doctrinacuriosa: @georgehotz prolly it's better if you mount your qira directroy so that that you don't need to clone the repo everytime
tomastakk: @Yellow_turd there's no 'best app development language'
CaptainAshtar: why you are not using anymore jupyter
Yellow_turd: @tomastakk I asked him what he thinks is the best, everyone has opinions maybe you dont have opinions tho
NoLimitFitness: PogChamp PogChamp
thuganalyst: Reuplods of this stream get tens of thousands of views on youtube lol
b_______________________b: @foxxible so yeah learn it but your gonna have to light read on memory managment and how it all works depending how you make your game in c
W1lkins: docker run -it
gazny: Dont think 3.8 hit stable
perkofficial: we need some george hotz emotes PogChamp
cIvIcbooks: docker run -it image bash
tomastakk: @Yellow_turd do you have yours?
Yellow_turd: yes
b_______________________b: @foxxible ya digg?
jfccoding: when you run qira are you running it on ubuntu or osx
foxxible: @b_______________________b oh okay, thank you
b_______________________b: jcgK
doctrinacuriosa: @georgehotz you dont ened to type apt-get all the time just apt is fine
robbsalm: ocd hits
JonThomasK: i take it my docker pull request will have to be redone :P
inshelootts: Hello
asthmaa: do you have thefuck installed?
b_______________________b: back seat coders in chat OMEGALUL
doctrinacuriosa: @georgehotz if you want absolute minimum you shouldn't be using ubuntu anyways, go with alpine
Hashcatcs: or arch
b_______________________b: @doctrinacuriosa tell him how to use the restroom too
adriaroms: or Windows
adriaroms: haha
Hashcatcs: or LFS
CaptainAshtar: @georgehotz why you are not using jupyter anymore?
doctrinacuriosa: @b_______________________b we got joker here
Hashcatcs: no we dont do that here
foxubu: Windows 10 Linux Subsystem
foxubu: Too poor for Mac :Z
mikestrike406: How do you type so damn fast?
adriaroms: Mac Hardware with Windows 10
eduardoadf1: nice haircut
JonThomasK: NotLikeThis
doctrinacuriosa: omg this is retarded
EkkoTheUnforgiven: hello there
brotas_: hello do you want to 1v1 me fortnite
doctrinacuriosa: im out bye
robbsalm: chill guys
Mac_33: I tried submodules once, it's pretty nifty
nick_porta: hi
b_______________________b: @nick_porta hey jcgK
chorbo123: george when are you gonna play LoL again
PixelogicDev: hiya @georgehotz - So super random question, do you usually have numbers like this while programming?
darthsergious: what color scheme is it?
b_______________________b: @darthsergious diarrhea
adriaroms: @b_______________________b no, diarrhea v2
aresfour: whats hackerman hacking on? :)
davidsit_site: qira
mikestrike406: hey @georgehotz why'd you move comma.ai to san diego?
SnakeOneMLG: @mikestrike406 there is an article about it
b_______________________b: qira Pog
adriaroms: why not CEO anymore? Exit?
ikoakmaindehoas: Excuse me while I use GIMP to create a command line interface to backtrace the killer's DNS ping in HTML.
cl_anubis: wut? not ceo?
adriaroms: yeah, why not CEO?
b_______________________b: too many new frogs jcgD
robbsalm: ahahah da heck
twiggy_io: He hasn't been ceo for awhile.
m0etaz: he hired a ceo
kanogger: the frog is a symbol of racism
kurumuz12: he is not being the ceo is old news
twiggy_io: He probably just didn't want to take that role.
adriaroms: yeah yeah, ik but he sell the co?
davidsit_site: too ADHD to have investor confidence, hired CEO= responsibilities managed?
JonThomasK: use a dog
fission1110: CEO is stressful and boring hah
foxubu: @adriaroms No, he’s now head of research
JonThomasK: eat it
adriaroms: ok
twiggy_io: It just takes awhile to herd cattle.
SnakeOneMLG: TriHard
hackyhacks: I've never herded cattle, but I worked on a farm as a teenager and was chased by a bull while changing his salt block.
SnakeOneMLG: is this TriHard friendly chat? TriHard
kanogger: TriHard
SnakeOneMLG: @kanogger cmonBruh
foxubu: @snakeonemlg Christian channel
b_______________________b: TriHard 7
davidsit_site: @snakeonemlg agreed.
kanogger: @SnakeOneMLG what's wrong brother? TriHard
barathrumberdem: what s he codin
SnakeOneMLG: "@kanogger " more like "ka TriHard"
SnakeOneMLG: "@kanogger " more like "ka TriHard "
SnakeOneMLG: RIP
davidsit_site: pre quantum practice debugger @barathrumberdem
Airfrischung: what kind of macbook are you using?
barathrumberdem: @davidsit_site aight that's coool
Keyeh: i think he uses a big imac not sure though
Mac_33: @Keyeh iMacs don't have a battery in 'em
davidsit_site: @barathrumberdem called qira. find if on github. Google geohot qira
SnakeOneMLG: 13 inch macbook
davidsit_site: find it
Keyeh: @Mac_33 thats true, didn't notice it :)
wisdom_tgo: Is he reading chat?
davidsit_site: "patch seems to apply cleanly "
dorkmo: tesla is sueing zoox
b_______________________b: I would love to George review Ghidra LUL
foxubu: Too many frame drops. Can’t follow you typing :Z
molehero: :q
wisdom_tgo: George are you Jewish?
bcmijk: Stutters here and there.
b_______________________b: @dorkmo logistic secrets jcgD
quillford: stream is smooth
asthmaa: he's too fast writing
Dsplits: bro frames are really dropping
Dsplits: I thought you had the best internet in the country
onemarko: he should ditch that mac
revolutionist123: 3rd stream in a row PogChamp
JonThomasK: lol
foxubu: 13 inch MacBook 5k monitor (for the record)
asthmaa: drugs?
jellyjar: frequent streams and a haircut???? that cant be geohot
bcmijk: Making him work LUL
Masplus: Wire of the gods solving framedrops
molehero: wire Pog
m0etaz: stream piano
oddtechno: Hey Ludde
javadragoniv: lmao do u play the piano?
Keyeh: we back
phatgary: all good
Dsplits: damn twitch hit us with the ad
lightofhel1: yo
twiggy_io: @davidsit_site nah its you.
kanogger: Back
alxhotel: Back
jfccoding: back
kozgn: @georgehotz probably your gpu sucks
John_DiResta: oh hello
JonThomasK: its a cpu problem from obs. Have to lower the input size of video
kanogger: but still dropping framed :(
cl_anubis: yoyo wb
jfccoding: no
WASDTeam: we back fo good
Dsplits: no
Dsplits: still laggy
barathrumberdem: whats his ip :D
cl_anubis: still laggy
lightofhel1: we back and drops back too
chorbo123: framedrop now 20% omegalul
NonTrivial778: do you use a password manager?
NonTrivial778: it's fine
funwayz: 10% increase
Yanisduc2: hi people out there
P3droPL: its not laggy - just dropped frames
nmuntz_: it's much better now
IndoPridePinoy: download some ram
NonTrivial778: yea
kozgn: @georgehotz check your system resources and maybe change to hardware rendering
zgamer0123: I think it's a liiittle bit better
quillford: it’s good enough
JonThomasK: lower resolution down from 1920
JonThomasK: will fix it
psychosocial1810: tell them instagram hoes to get off your internet
John_DiResta: yeah it just dropped frames
NonTrivial778: La puta madre geohot
cl_anubis: @georgehotz looks better now
Yellow_turd: @georgehotz reduce the resolution of your camera. it works for me
Keyeh: LMAO
zgamer0123: OMG
JonThomasK: TAIWAN Pog
zacoaa: LMFAO
deR_Ed: Mr Worldwide xD
U_P_I_A: lol
cl_anubis: that was a hyped end
twiggy_io: Lol I lost it.
W1lkins: even laggier LUL
gazny: LUL
funwayz: 0% OMEGALUL
Keyeh: no frames dropping PogChamp
John_DiResta: can't wait for the crispness
Dsplits: bro so much better now
kanogger: Zero PogChamp
WASDTeam: while building a low level debugger
serhejenos: 30 fps
toolegit2quit_: high quality too
JonThomasK: TAIWAN #1 TAIWAN #1 TAIWAN #1 TAIWAN #1 TAIWAN #1 TAIWAN #1
chorbo123: that end tho lmao
zgamer0123: GG thanks :D
cl_anubis: boiiiiis
lightofhel1: LMFAO
revolutionist123: LUL
jcream: LUL LUL
John_DiResta: niiiiceeeeeee
lightofhel1: yo
e2yub: it is simply beautiful
serhejenos: Why frames are caped at 30?
P0LY: FeelsGoodMan
alxhotel: no log
JonThomasK: TAIWAN #1
mungo_mungo: go back to taiwan
toolegit2quit_: Church of Taiwan Server
WASDTeam: now we want 5k @60fps
Keyeh: you can also increase the bitrate now
WASDTeam: lol
cIvIcbooks: bring back taiwan
revolutionist123: 30 year old get exited with changing server LUL
serhejenos: ahaha
funwayz: I miss drops :/
e2yub: So smooth
John_DiResta: daaaaaaaaaaaam
psychosocial1810: you dont really need 60 fps watching programming
lightofhel1: 0.0% feels good
JonThomasK: exactly
Keyeh: monkaS
ikoakmaindehoas: what are you drinking?
P0LY: FeelsBadMan
Zeldorino: LUL
Sandoww: What codec does twitch use?
deadpool_reynolds: whiskey
jellyjar: 2irl4me
bcmijk: Now it's too smooth, I miss them drops FeelsBadMan
kanogger: harsh words
e2yub: yikes
MatiGoG: FeelsBadMan
erichtp: nice haircut you've been on a roll with the streams!
revolutionist123: FeelsBadMan
asthmaa: whiskey?
zacoaa: LMFAO
twiggy_io: h256
robbsalm: " i dont think it gets better" takes a rope
P0LY: FeelsGoodMan
chorbo123: this isn't @georgehotz stream without the dropped frames
onemarko: what is the motivation behind qira anyway?
dorkmo: it gets shitty TM
MatiGoG: FeelsGoodMan Clap
bosapiutsa: much better pog
foxasmr: Doomer vs twitch
WASDTeam: went tomta
serhejenos: Pepesad
WASDTeam: went to taiwan, never got back
Keyeh: it gets worse but at least we have geo streaming FeelsAmazingMan
magician2378: which pixel is george?
RomanNYC: dam this is crispy
qrln: s/o to twitch
erichtp: new chair PogChamp
Dsplits: @georgehotz are you working on any other projects?
zacoaa: LUL
kanogger: BibleThump
Admiralkheir: are your repositories private?
lightofhel1: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
bcmijk: bcmijk subscribed at Tier 1.
bcmijk: More internet monies.
revolutionist123: How to get a girlfriend as a hacker 101 LUL
chorbo123: what keyboard is he using
Zeldorino: monkaS
zacoaa: boom shes yours
MRSIMSIM2: just talk 4Head
kanogger: i want to be your girlfriend :)
magician2378: george, do you want to be my girlfriend?
lightofhel1: B)
foxubu: @kanogger female detected 🤓
bcmijk: Last I saw he was using the Leopold FC980M @chorbo123
Keyeh: just have LOTS of money
MatiGoG: be fake FeelsBadMan just to get a gf
revolutionist123: Now i can lose my virginity bro thank u!
kanogger: @foxubu yes but only dating guys with more than 10k followers sorry
chorbo123: cool @bcmijk
Ex0diaaa: @georgehotz where to start to be a good programmer?
robbsalm: create an app thats worth 10 mil, girls will find you
bcmijk: @chorbo123 or.. FC750R, can't remember.
MatiGoG: @Ex0diaaa first you need to start lmao
Protoxus: Hello jgrHI
foxubu: @kanogger If that’s your metric, I give a sh!t about dating you :D
Hamled2: yes!
Keyeh: @georgehotz have you ever compete in programming contests?
revolutionist123: If it works dont touch it
lightofhel1: maybe switch to latest qemu?
Ex0diaaa: @MatiGoG I say in relation to content to study.
Hamled2: RealTargetDisas is some PHP shit...
phatgary: which keyboard do you use?
IWasnotDemi: @georgehotz what's your wpm when typing?
dorkmo: hes not writing a book
kozgn: @georgehotz does qira work on windows, do you plan to support it on?
Infinitelym: is this really basic programming?
m0etaz: lol
m0etaz: it's the most advanced programming
Keyeh: its basic dude
jfccoding: trying to install this on mac getting this for an error ./pin-latest/source/include/pin/level_base.PLH:64:10: fatal error: 'string' file not found #include <string>
Fooly27: @Infinitelym very basic if you cant understand this give up
jfccoding: anyone know anything?
hoffs: a is a good variable
dorkmo: basic like a basic bitch
revolutionist123: all
Hamled2: a for assembly...
robbsalm: mips architecture bois
PhillipWei: it's within an ifdef
kanogger: I use a in minified javascript Kappa
dorkmo: a is for apple
Hamled2: reassingment probably doesn't count as use?
robbsalm: a is for aidontunderstand
Zeldorino: george is going from startup ceo to professional twitch streamer SeemsGood
PhillipWei: reassignment does mean use
OFFICER_KKONA: what keybaord are you using?
Hamled2: why does it count as being used? it wouldn't necessarily be read, right?
Jewishrambo: this code looks trash
onemarko: man you learn to code cleanly when you have to go back and read your own code
robbsalm: @georgehotz dont you get eyesache after hours on an such an high constrat theme
alienware997: alienware997 subscribed at Tier 3.
PhillipWei: @hamled2 looks like you're correct
Hamled2: did the compile errors go away? George might still be wrong 😂
alienware997: Btw i was the guy who asked for the better Installer, thanks for your work, really appreciate it! And here comes my Level 3 Subscription!
shrek_361: George the GOAT
LookOverHeHe: Geoooooo
hoffs: tier 3 is big money 25 usd sub
tempor1s: Tier 3 means it costs $25 instead of 5 bucks
Hamled2: nice
Differential: basically means they paid $25 to sub
knilecrack: Sup
knilecrack: What are you doing?
alienware997: To be clear i paid in Euro, so its 24,99€:D
ikoakmaindehoas: thats hella expensive
Zeldorino: You get 5x the money for tier 3
TwitchFoxy: TwitchFoxy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
TwitchFoxy: George is such a rabbit hole, I was watching Jailbreaking the simulation and counterfactual regret minimization... now I am here
Rlchibi: I was!
Keyeh: HeyGuys
bcmijk: Taiwan #1
P0LY: VoHiYo
cIvIcbooks: bring back taiwan
ikoakmaindehoas: HeyGuys
e2yub: #1
kanogger: ✋
serhejenos: I was
boy_milk: i missed it :(
dorkmo: fucking nuts taiwan #1
GiGnX12: VoHiYo
phatgary: MaxLOL
deadpool_reynolds: ( · · ) /
toolegit2quit_: if you know you know
RigzGame: VoHiYo
revolutionist123: HeyGuys
hyldee: Fucking miss Taiwan
Zeldorino: 🙋♂️
e2yub: what a service
serhejenos: Go with Russia next time
twiggy_io: HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys
benjaminr42: VoHiYo
Hamled2: red diffs yeah
frederik_diamond: Hey
Hamled2: cut out all that old rotten code
frederik_diamond: it's my first time watching your stream:)
bagaytht: whats your keyboard and mouse ?
hoffs: 25k commits behind
twiggy_io: Why do so many people care about what keyboard he uses?
RigzGame: idk
Hamled2: why didn't you need those anymore
RigzGame: it's useless to know x)
Hamled2: ah cool
RigzGame: use your keyboard to make something interesting :D
Hamled2: are you doing a custom qemu
ActionIsComing: Hi man
coProof: Can I pip install qira yetttt???!
Hamled2: but it does need to be built just for qira, no prebuilt distro version?
ikoakmaindehoas: gimme dem jack daniels
hoffs: that tea
Hamled2: ohh, so qemu doesn't have a "recording" layer at all?
chelsiquixote: did geohot shave his dome piece?
donaldtheduck2000: can you use qira to reverse engineer the simulation yet?
Zeldorino: 🐦
robbsalm: with assembly we will escape the simulation
Hamled2: lol I have a friend who works at GitHub, not sure that's always as true as you'd think :D
saulgd: i feel so out of my depth watching george LUL
RudeCoffee: This really makes me want to eat a taco
Biffingtonn: @RudeCoffee yeah true actually
brisingr1031: @georgehotz still using your hkkb?
dorkmo: DoritosChip TheIlluminati
alex_sez: have u tried Ghidra? if so, what is your opinion of it?
s1ug: damn. thought his hat said REE.
s1ug: was gonna ask for link.
ActionIsComing: i would never touch nsa software
alex_sez: lol
Protoxus: @actioniscoming All software is NSA software TheIlluminati
ActionIsComing: cmonBruh
Protoxus: jgrREE
jfccoding: its the nsa if your really that scared about installing the software they don't need you to install anything if they really want to get on your systems
JonThomasK: i take it my docker pull request wasnt good enough? @georgehotz
nmuntz_: @georgehotz just change that line with python3 -m venv venv
Sportmann941: hi, what are you trying to programm rn? @georgehotz
Protoxus: @jfccoding True. Just read Vault9. Ez hackerino
knilecrack: how did you fix frame dropping?
Protoxus: @sportmann941 Qira. The description is on the GitHub url
TheBigK02: could u move back up to 1080p then?
alex_sez: did u play pwnable.tw while u were in taiwan? Kappa
JonThomasK: i fixed a lot of this in the docker PR. the pip install is using pip2 on ubuntu. Change it to pip3
pavankumarp: how is he executing commands in same shellwhile a script is executing, any idea ?. Or am I overthinking and it is just alt tab ?
twiggy_io: tmux
nanodanger7: it's screen
pavankumarp: oh okay, tmux.
shepard_commander62: did python3 split the community?
TheBigK02: its like systemd splitted the linux community :)
mikey9988: python 3 PepeHands
lucas9o: what keyboard do you use?
TheBigK02: i would also like to know @lucas9o
Hamled2: ewwww
Hamled2: so huge
Nesquik80: yo yo
Nesquik80: @georgehotz how's life
Protoxus: @nesquik80 Simulated. jgrTARD
JonThomasK: docker image prune..... no s on images
Nesquik80: @georgehotz not using Startpage anymore?
ikoakmaindehoas: you can run docker build with the --no-cache flag
Hamled2: apparently it's related to building a "device tree"?
TheBigK02: atleast he tries which is kinda cool
Hamled2: Not sure if that's like the hierarchy of components in your computer (USB and PCI buses and their attached stuff?)
Protoxus: !voteban onebitbrain
anatoly1974: where's the hair dude ???
TheBigK02: i like the challange beeing insa famous for the sake of it... or for a secret plan to bash tesla :)
Protoxus: @onebitbrain jgrGame
0TestUser: are u trying to get insta famous for the girls ? Kappa
WASDTeam: yup, its a descriptor of all the devices and their addrs for driver init and stuff
Hamled2: @georgehotz why do you need to compile qemu in the docker image? can't it be build somewhere and downloaded as a pre-made image (maybe a docker layer?)
Nesquik80: @georgehotz not using Startpage anymore?
Simon_AA: use alpine instead of ubuntu?
donaldtheduck2000: why do you want to be instagram famous bro
donaldtheduck2000: u just need a select few followers that respect your work
Protoxus: @donaldtheduck2000 We'll know when it happens
mikey9988: using safari monkaS
Protoxus: I use Chrome Canary and Firefox Developer Edition interchangably jgrThink
TheBigK02: what do u use @mikey9988 ... i used to use chrome... but im migrating back to ff... but i feel like both arent gr8
serhejenos: What about tensorflow 2.0?
anatoly1974: can somebody explain what project is George working on this looks like mandarin ??? @georgehotz
Simon_AA: Maybe they simple hired better PR people?
dorkmo: i banned a man in reno just to watch him die
Protoxus: @anatoly1974 Just go to the GitHub link in the title, everything is explained there
mikey9988: i use chrome monkaS @TheBigK02
Hamled2: @georgehotz is qemu only built when compiling the docker image, or will everybody that installs via docker going to end up having it compiled on their machine as well?
anatoly1974: thx @Protoxus
Protoxus: @mikey9988 Consider opting for Chrome Canary if you're in webdev
Protoxus: SeemsGood
knilecrack: how about you do multi stage build?
TheBigK02: as i saw a freaking virus scanner built into that freaking browser... i thought... FUCK THIS... im out
favvs13: TriHard gang
mikey9988: imagine using windows command prompt
RudeCoffee: wiki, "Qi'ra is a fictional character in the Star Wars franchise"
mikey9988: after years of bash
alex_sez: its jar jar binks cousin
W1lkins: Where's the Mac Miller
Aer0skull: XD
TheBigK02: i mean... the powershell has a worse reputation that it acutally is
Protoxus: @w1lkins He died
TheBigK02: its not perfect... but its atleast not weird batch shit
Protoxus: @thebigk02 Batch-shit crazy :^)
mikey9988: Borne again shell is PogChamp
donaldtheduck2000: it's good but they tried to add their own touch to it, so they screwed it up
donaldtheduck2000: but it was a good starting point
TheBigK02: i mean ... what didnt they screw up... the only usable protocol MS has is RDP... and that protocol is bought from citrix :D
Hamled2: yeah don't do update
Hamled2: that should be the system owner's decision
Hamled2: I hate how homebrew runs an update before every command
TheBigK02: but i actually admire the way they went with the surface pro... i actually like the device and the idea behind it...
TheBigK02: if there would be a linux on it... it would be a great device :D
pspxdiso: @georgehotz Hey Mr. Balls, how far along are you with the port to Python 3?
TheBigK02: isnt he pretty much done? i might be wrong here...
Thorstein47: i dont understand anyrhing what is this
TheBigK02: what is what... qira? is a debugger...
donaldtheduck2000: Is it a debugger or does it hook into a debugger?
donaldtheduck2000: I thought it's just a GUI
RudeCoffee: "QIRA is a competitor to strace and gdb"
ericswenson15: yo do you do any iot stuff?
Hamled2: it works with qemu to do debugging donaldtheduck2000
donaldtheduck2000: ah
shepard_commander62: heard of ROS?
Hamled2: it's not the same exact kind of debugging you can do with gdb, but it's got some stuff gdb doesn't have (viewing the entire execution timeline like a video you can scrub back and forth)
donaldtheduck2000: didn't know that qemu did debugging
Hamled2: it doesn't, I think this is based on a patch he wrote
Hamled2: to record all the instructions that get executed
donaldtheduck2000: oh
donaldtheduck2000: interesting
Hamled2: it's probably closer to some profiling tools
Thorstein47: can someone explain what is he doing?
sdak006: @georgehotz is there any reason you are pulling full git history in your docker image? Seems wasteful
pspxdiso: @Thorstein47 He is busting balls
mikey9988: is Geohots on an actual mac or is it a hackintosh ?
ericswenson15: would you be interested in microservice development for https://www.swensonhe.com/
knilecrack: mac i believe
donaldtheduck2000: there is a dynamic to static converter I believe
TheBigK02: hes using a macbook pro 2017 version i believe (13 inch)
r1c1c: why can't i see the chat
more_bacon: Geeeeeoooorrrrgggeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
twiggy_io: Because you are broken.
mikey9988: thanks @TheBigK02
r1c1c: Is it because I haven't subscribed?
W1lkins: You need to follow on Instagram first r1c1c
r1c1c: followed already
ActionIsComing: no loss for you, nothing smart in chat
ActionIsComing: czySMUG
kei86: "ex sued by Sony" LUL
serhejenos: You are almost there
Nesquik80: @georgehotz do you do some javascript?
NonTrivial778: why i am slow at logical thinking? am i a low iq?
ActionIsComing: yea
NonTrivial778: LUL
Luki512: Hello @ all
twiggy_io: Hello @Luki512
Networks: hello epic fortnite gamers
serhejenos: No
W1lkins: no
cIvIcbooks: https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/b51w74/george_hotz_1_million_in_2019/
serhejenos: Kappa
JonThomasK: k
Prest0n1337: hell nah
mikey9988: LUL
ActionIsComing: no
NonTrivial778: i'm on fedora and its fucking painfull to install qira
P0LY: monkaS
alienware997: I will try!
shepard_commander62: twitch testing, i am watching from a bus though
Aer0skull: i have to reboot for that
mikey9988: my machine just blew up, messaging from my phone Kappa
serhejenos: Will it install on windows? I don't have anything other right now
Prest0n1337: jk I might try sometime later
r1c1c: george wouldn't be george anymore once he gets 1M followers :(
JonThomasK: i did a version where i made qira run your binary in the container, obviously only works with linux binaries but it was cool
Prest0n1337: life long loser trys to make github commit
mikey9988: He'll be the george he wanted to be, but the one you didn't want to see him become @JonThomasK
more_bacon: George, how do I donate to your church? I have many lambs
kozgn: @georgehotz this error occured on windows when runned install.bat
kozgn: sk-socketio pillow pyelftools socketIO-client pydot ipaddr capstone ./qiradb
JonThomasK: hrrm? @mikey9988
480i: Wait. There’s a church now??
donaldtheduck2000: I think the church was a joke
NonTrivial778: installing fucking qira ....
kei86: 480i : Makes more sense if you saw his SXSW talk
serhejenos: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
JonThomasK: Time to sue bois
Prest0n1337: trademark it
mikey9988: sorry i meant the @ the guy above you please ignore @JonThomasK
alienware997: This is my error: that’s the error I get: make: *** No rule to make target `trace/generated-events.h‘, needed by `Makefile‘. Stop. make: *** Waiting for unfinished jobs.... make: *** [config-host.mak] Error 1
donaldtheduck2000: how would it work
kozgn: @georgehotz oh actually ican install on windows with windows subsytem or github bash lol
Meapzor: qira still first here
r1c1c: @mikey9988 yeah i mean he will still be the george he wanted to be but not on livestreams
Hamled2: @sdak006 I stepped away for a bit, did George address your question about just doing a shallow clone?
Cape_clear: where is your hair?
knilecrack: should this work on mac without issues?
donaldtheduck2000: upload binary, send it to a qemu instance on the cloud?
alienware997: Macbook pro 2014 majove
Murgio: lamo where is your jair
Murgio: lmao
Murgio: hair
GenBurnside: help. trying to convert a .rdb into a usable format
zenkai_oogway: can anyone tell me a basic description of what hes building? I missed the last few streams
cIvIcbooks: docker build bombed out
knilecrack: ah yeah
GenBurnside: roots 2 genealogy save file (90's)
cIvIcbooks: The command '/bin/sh -c cd tracers && ./qemu_build.sh' returned a non-zero code: 137
mikey9988: what's the GitHub username ?
Aer0skull: k i'm cloning it
GenBurnside: trying to get the genealogy data
serhejenos: @zenkai_oogway updates his program named qira and made for debagging purposes
mikey9988: nvm is geohot
W1lkins: TriHard
zenkai_oogway: @serhejenos ty, I shouldve read the title lol
revolutionist123: monkaS
ActionIsComing: HOLUP cmonBruh ^
donaldtheduck2000: is this Ubuntu?
NonTrivial778: I run ./qira -s /bin/ls and nothing show up on 127.0.0.1:3002
revolutionist123: @donaldtheduck2000 look top left
b_______________________b: @donaldtheduck2000 mac but it's all the same Only diff is max is BSD and not linux
b_______________________b: max* not max
alex_sez: max
kei86: distantly BSD
donaldtheduck2000: yea just thought he said that it doesn't run on mac
knilecrack: yes it doesnt
b_______________________b: so is he using QEMU for cross-platform development or another reason?
kei86: donaldtheduck2000 : He's also ssh-ing into something and using docker
donaldtheduck2000: right that what I was referring to
Nesquik80: @georgehotz do you prefer mac or linux?
Aer0skull: how you have an install.bat and not Windows supported
knilecrack: but you should be able to clone this to docker ubuntu image and give it a shot
donaldtheduck2000: cool
Hamled2: @georgehotz what branch are you working on
kei86: Aer0skull : maybe it simply echos "Not for windows dude!" :D
NonTrivial778: File "/home/anon/qira/venv/lib64/python3.7/os.py", line 594, in _execvpe exec_func(file, *argrest) FileNotFoundError: [Errno 2] No such file or directory
Aer0skull: no, i check it
Aer0skull: x)
e2yub: trying it right now
NonTrivial778: no I am on fedora
kei86: @georgehotz : Did you see cIvIcbooks 's error up above on Docker? "The command '/bin/sh -c cd tracers && ./qemu_build.sh' returned a non-zero code: 137"
Hamled2: NonTrivial778 can you post the entire stacktrace to Gist?
alienware997: Okay when Mac not supported i have to fire up my Ubuntu VM....
NonTrivial778: start the server on 127.0.0.1:3002 but nothing shows up
Hamled2: @georgehotz would you mind if I made a PR to add Arch stuff back into the install script?
donaldtheduck2000: can you run qemu inside a vm?
Aer0skull: util/memfd.c:43:12: error: static declaration of ‘memfd_create’ follows non-static declaration
knilecrack: yuo should be able
knilecrack: are you using vmware or virtualbox?
donaldtheduck2000: virtualbox
alienware997: I will try with vmware
knilecrack: one moment
Aer0skull: on Ubuntu 18.10
twiggy_io: @alienware997 why not use the docker image?
donaldtheduck2000: if I remember correctly you can't nest virtual machines
knilecrack: you need to enable that extended features in processor tab for VM
kei86: @cIvIcbooks : You figure that error out?
Yanisduc2: util/memfd.c:43:12: error: static declaration of ‘memfd_create’ follows non-static declaration static int memfd_create(const char *name, unsigned int flags)
donaldtheduck2000: oh
Yanisduc2: got this error message on windows subsystem for linux with ubuntu 18.04
anstefa: whats up
Max__PWR: Yo, complete noob over here. Is this python ?
W1lkins: yes
kozgn: @georgehotz (/usr/local/bin:/usr/bin:/bin:/usr/local/sbin:/usr/bin/site_perl:/usr/bin/vendor_perl:/usr/bin/core_perl) *** You'll need to install Ubuntu or get a working build env for qemu and python yourself *** install.sh: line 12: tracers/qemu/qira-i386: No such file or directory building QEMU Cloning into 'qemu'... remote: Enumerating objects: 4461, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (4461/4461), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (4056/4056), done. remote: Total 4461 (delta 562), reus
Hamled2: some is python, some is bash script, some is C
kozgn: sorry for spam
Aer0skull: @Yanisduc2 same
ericswenson15: sorry kinda random but would you be interested in an iot project for simple human?
Trenz2: @georgehotz when u're gonna do some bountys or ctf bro?
NonTrivial778: https://i.imgur.com/uJ6m6Gp.png
twiggy_io: @ericswenson15 he built a startup. I don't think he wants to work for you.
Max__PWR: what languange would you guys recommend to get started with to get into programming?
Max__PWR: I heard python is a good start
JonThomasK: if you hate yourself, javascript
donaldtheduck2000: it's good
donaldtheduck2000: also asm
kei86: python is good
knilecrack: c if you hate yourself
MatiGoG: 4 errors on ubuntu cant install
anstefa: How many computer languages can you type? :D
ericswenson15: it's not my company
anstefa: or speak
ericswenson15: but true
alienware997: @twiggy_io are you running qira on that? I mean i have a Pc only for my VM's here and its up all the time so i thought the easiest way is to install qira there an access it with my mac over ssh...
donaldtheduck2000: start with a scripting language, spoil yourself, then learn C, then ASM
donaldtheduck2000: then forget all that and code in python
ericswenson15: lol
akvana5656: Hiii
ericswenson15: or you can try spanish
W1lkins: TriHard
twiggy_io: @alienware997 Thats the best part of docker. It runs like a vm so you can just boot it up locally can connect to the local vm.
donaldtheduck2000: if you want to get fancy learn LISP
umps: why code in vim rather than an IDE with vim keybinds?
Max__PWR: ok, I think Im going with spanish then. Thanks!
donaldtheduck2000: then realise life is too short
ericswenson15: lol
donaldtheduck2000: and code python
knilecrack: so you can learn better
ActionIsComing: popo
mikey9988: recommending asm monkaS @donaldtheduck2000
W1lkins: why do you need an ide umps
alienware997: @twiggy_io thanks for the Tip, havn't used it till today, will now definitely change:)
anstefa: expirence in the dark web?
Simon_AA: with all of this problems with different OS, you say that docker is preferred method of installation
anstefa: expirience in the dark web?
W1lkins: anstefa stop spamming
kozgn: https://pastebin.com/dQHYNVR4 this occured in arch-linux using pacman @georgehotz
mikey9988: any java programmers here?
xtyonx: ohhhhh the hear cut
umps: why don't you need an ide @W1lkins
anstefa: @W1lkins lol
donaldtheduck2000: seriously just learn python, you only need need C/C to optimize python
twiggy_io: @kozgn You'll need to install Ubuntu or get a working build env for qemu and python yourself *
NonTrivial778: fix your shit
twiggy_io: Its the first line.
MatiGoG: util/memfd.c:43:12: error: static declaration of ‘memfd_create’ follows non-static declaration static int memfd_create(const char *name, unsigned int flags)
donaldtheduck2000: unless you want to do low level programming, like write debuggers, compilers etc
Hamled2: @georgehotz the tracers/qemu/whatever symlinks don't seem to work
kozgn: @twiggy_io cant do that inside script?
ffthgezgxjkndd: when does python 2.7 stop getting supported?
W1lkins: umps there's no point in discussing if you answer a question with the opposite of the question
knilecrack: i started docker thing now
knilecrack: it's working
knilecrack: i mean it's compiling ...
ericswenson15: poodles
umps: @W1lkins you literally did the same exact thing LUL
ericswenson15: LUL
W1lkins: umps :)
Hamled2: @georgehotz I think you need to do an install script change to check if [ -e ] before running the script ot check for return value of 1`
tybutnowyoudie: @ffthgezgxjkndd Jan 2020
serhejenos: @ffthgezgxjkndd they said in 2020 but, it's "simbolic" they will probably continue to support way past that time
knilecrack: this mac is crap so it's still working
Hamled2: @georgehotz For the qemu symlinks, I mean
HardDenmark: hi guys
NonTrivial778: I did git clone qira
NonTrivial778: ooohhh
alluxua: Geohot, why you put on a hat in the room?
twiggy_io: To block out the haters.
Sparking: swag points
HardDenmark: looking cool
umps: did he ever get his food
alluxua: Who hate him? He is so adorable
Hamled2: @georgehotz The tracers/qemu directory has several symlinks to qemu binaries, in current master commit
Hamled2: @georgehotz and the install script is trying to run one of them to check if QEMu was built, but the symlink doens't go anywhere
Hamled2: @georgehotz so you get an error message about file not found
umps: oh u got a haircut
SlightR6: Do you ever plan to bypass anti-cheats?
Hamled2: I guess it's just unnecessary error? it was in everyone's output when they tried to run the script
Hamled2: okay
Farafire: hello from spain!
ericswenson15: he would be the best engineer ever
ericswenson15: prolly
Hamled2: @georgehotz would you accept a PR to add back Arch support?
Meapzor: Chrome DansGame
anstefa: what is qira?
twiggy_io: A new star wars character.
ericswenson15: oh nice
twiggy_io: Kappa
Hamled2: Of course
ffthgezgxjkndd: yeah shes natelie portmans daughter
ericswenson15: yay copyrgiht music
NonTrivial778: You'll need to install Ubuntu or get a working build env for qemu and python yourself LUL
Yanisduc2: ubuntu 18.04 not supportet?
ericswenson15: LUL
nizero: nice haircut george
SlightR6: Will you ever plan to bypass anti-cheats
ericswenson15: lol aggreed
knilecrack: shitty world
oX333: VAY VAY VAY SIHHATLER OLSUN REİS
nizero: george are you going to move to san diego with the rest of the comma ai team ?
ericswenson15: interesting
Yanisduc2: no one
ffthgezgxjkndd: so deep
ffthgezgxjkndd: lol
Hamled2: They'll put you in solitary confinement like Schwartz :(
ericswenson15: very true
RealGamer613: hit the weed one time
eazzycs: @oX333 dün
ericswenson15: i steal the words
mikey9988: LUL ? @RealGamer613
alluxua: Hi geohot, you got beautiful voice. Can you sing the song ‘ let her go’ by the passenger?
ericswenson15: LUL
mikey9988: Free Shkreli PogChamp
ericswenson15: move to country w/out extradition
eazzycs: @oX333 dün dedim ki git tras ol olmus xd
alienware997: @twiggy_io setting up Docker right now:D
krasbolle: same
oX333: @eazzycs :dDDD
xtyonx: well say Hi they are watching you :)
donaldtheduck2000: Hey bro
akvana5656: Selammmm
alluxua: Watch YouTube and sing let her go by passenger
eazzycs: beyler bu pic ne yapiyo anlamadim gitti
donaldtheduck2000: do you think the simulation is using Spatial locality?
eazzycs: gitsin namaz kilsin ibadet etsin bos seyler ile ugrasmasin
donaldtheduck2000: I was thinking about this the other day
donaldtheduck2000: maybe that's why synchronicity happens
donaldtheduck2000: because what you think about and what happens and what already happened are stored in the same location
donaldtheduck2000: to conserve space
keepingtrckofthisacct: oooh man, how much did i miss?!
RealGamer613: hit the weed one time
keepingtrckofthisacct: !uptime
ActionIsComing: czyUNI
P0LY: :D
keepingtrckofthisacct: how long has he been on?
donaldtheduck2000: ok bro :(
erichtp: 1 hour, 44 minutes, 55 seconds @keepingtrckofthisacct
keepingtrckofthisacct: @erichtp thanks!
lostchange: bamDog bam1 bamPog bam3
montecarlo: HAIRCUT NICE
mikey9988: LUL @RealGamer613
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz Dam dude you got a haircut, looking fresh mah dude!
tybutnowyoudie: almost 10k PogChamp
alienware997: Which Docker Image do you use? Sorry for dumb questions @twiggy_io
lostchange: just followed bamSellout bamSellout
Meapzor: what kind of content should we expect if we follow?
Hamled2: python ontop of unicorn? or just straight python?
JonThomasK: i build the stages because eventually you can have a base image thats built once and a qira base that just updates pip dependcies. Eventually you can mount the binary onto the container and wont need ANY install scripts at all
Protoxus: You gotta beat the Instagram algorithm. Daily uploads, use the right SEO hashtags, git gut
Xaotic: what is his computer ? setup ?
E1337YT: tomcr00s3 looks different than in the movies
Hamled2: ANGR only does symbolic execution right @georgehotz
alienware997: @twiggy_io got it by my own. sorry for that dumb question
Hamled2: I guess it's just angr
Hamled2: @georgehotz or is the "program instrumentation" bit what you would use for Qira's tracer?
Thomasbrah: is that chair comfortable or is it just all looks?
AshfaqSeyad: hey man
AshfaqSeyad: u accept questions?
yoshimoto555: I wish python had a good debugger
santi_264: favourite book?
Protoxus: @santi_264 Try "The Ego & Its Own" by Max Stirner
0TestUser: 0TestUser subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Yellow_turd: sellout LUL
OFFICER_KKONA: capitalism in a nutshell FeelsBadMan
Trenz2: Jebaited
Tigerman143: sup geo
Protoxus: @yellow_turd That's capitalism for ya, buddy
Xaotic: FeelsBadMan
Trenz2: not making enough money question mark
Aer0skull: you just answered a non subscriber question
Yellow_turd: im not your buddy, pal
santi_264: damn yellow chill
jeann2019: Hery put music in backgroud men
Protoxus: I don't like your South Park memes, and I'm not your pal, guy
r1c1c: <3
Yellow_turd: im not your guy, mister
Trenz2: i.m not your guy , buddy LUL
r1c1c: im not your guy, pal LUL
NonTrivial778: now I'll try install it on Linux Mint
Trenz2: i.m not our pal , hommie
alex_sez: ...
Hamled2: @georgehotz you said earlier the project is already ported to python 3, the install script is installing (I think) python 2.7 packages (like python python-dev and python-virtualenv) is this correct?
santi_264: can a subscriber ask him his favourite bbok
Xflagzzz: What are you programming?
serhejenos: Gift which keeps on giving
Hamled2: @georgehotz I mean, is my understanding correct?
GenBurnside: man
r1c1c: anyone can gift a me a sub
Protoxus: Non-subs are human trash jgrREE jgrREE jgrREE
Thomasbrah: subl
tybutnowyoudie: sublime?
GenBurnside: there is nothing on the internet on how to mess with an .rdb from the 1990s
fortnest: you look stupid in this cap, don't ban me pls
alluxua: You have nice hair and great eyes. Donot put in cap
0TestUser: are there any sub emotes ?
Protoxus: Pineapple on pizza is a ban-worthy opinion in the streams I usually watch.
xtyonx: don't encourage people to click ont he x button in real life !
alluxua: Do whatever to make you happy
NonTrivial778: we want to see bof exploits LUL
Hamled2: @georgehotz does Angr actually execute instructions in a sim like QEMU? doesn't look like it
Fulk33: @georgehotz what are your current plans for quira? can we help?
Hamled2: There's the symbolic executor, but isn't that much different from what QEMU is doing
NonTrivial778: works on linuxmint LUL https://i.imgur.com/NYeGCgb.png
bignobaoki: Hey man whats up!
Hamled2: Radare was built by people who used GDB and thought "This is too good of a user experience"
yoshimoto555: Lol that made my day
yrreseason: Ubuntu still your favourite distro ?
Hamled2: Does QEMU do the lifting to IR to help with execution? (e.g. then it implements its own VM for that IR)?
SlightR6: What is qira?
kozgn: @georgehotz i managed to get this far on arch-linux https://pastebin.com/J9KFeuf4
Hamled2: If you're using some other version of libc, how can you know that the execution results you're seeing in the sim are accurate?
gator____: @georgehotz hey man sorry if this is off topic, but how do you stay productive and fight distraction? procrastination seems to be my best friend these days and you seem like a productivity machine :D
ArcherCreatlol: qemu unicorn engine
Twitch0xme: @georgehotz are you planning to add remote debugging support to qira?
W1lkins: I do :)
Hamled2: That's a great summary
OmarBeBallin: I like pain :)
ericswenson15: good job
NonTrivial778: Gentoo is worse, emerge is a pain in the ass
NackterZeuS: of course I Like my life to be pain Kreygasm
PatriqDesigns: KISS
Hamled2: So Simple It Doesn't Work TM
juka_espada_quebrada: !uptime
alluxua: Sing a song, please
Ampalos23: forsen1 forsen2
davidb881: Lets port Internet into TempleOs
xstaubfinger: wut
ericswenson15: keep it simple cus im stupid
OmarBeBallin: forsen boys LULW
Nesquik80: you guys heard of article 13?
NonTrivial778: u like to fucking debug programs in ASM
W1lkins: It is quite funny though "Tries to keep it simple" rest of the news is manual interventions to keep your system up and running 4Head
alluxua: Your hair is way better looking than that cap
Hamled2: Lets write it georgehotz
Ampalos23: Hey guys can u tell me how to code a virtual girlfriend? forsenE
StanStill1710: whats a kernal
ericswenson15: popcorn
Bioaim7: yes
OmarBeBallin: im one of those guys who likes to rewrite everything.. so u know my opinion
Bioaim7: start it!
kingkontraa: Got a new haircut PogChamp
hyldee: do it, then ill follow you on instagram
PlayITBruiser: yeeeeeeeeaaaa
alluxua: Sing a song before code. Any song, please
twiggy_io: @georgehotz write it in go.
cIvIcbooks: time to hit that yerba
PlayITBruiser: code it with gucci gang
Hamled2: Like you're building a complete user-space loading system?
0TestUser: you have a netflix series to recommend ?
Ampalos23: rm -rf / forsenLewd
JumpTwiice: sup dudes
r1c1c: ANIME
PlayITBruiser: watch tombstone
ericswenson15: file size recommendation?
0TestUser: AYAYA
b4qazan: are you not too old to watch chineese cartoons?
th3_maj0r: death note the anime i hope
spoco: weebs FailFish
davidb881: we gonna write C?
PlayITBruiser: western movie
JumpTwiice: what we writing today?
Ampalos23: forsenPuke
Hamled2: @georgehotz would this usercorn-type tool you're talking about be something that worked to analyze windows binaries? It seems like 90% of the audience for analysis tools is people looking at windows malware...
ericswenson15: comments or long var and function names or both?
W1lkins: RIP fans
ericswenson15: LUL
r1c1c: Go watch The Promised Neverland
ericswenson15: ok thank you
tybutnowyoudie: apple doesn't do comments?
ericswenson15: robert martin says long var names
NonTrivial778: LIKE A BOSS
ericswenson15: idk
Bioaim7: LUL
Jewishrambo: Kappa
Jewishrambo: Kappa Kappa
Ampalos23: I read code to sleep
NonTrivial778: Andrew Tanenbaum is a good coder too
PlayITBruiser: gay comments
r1c1c: @tybutnowyoudie they don't because their codes are already readable
Bioaim7: KappaPride
ericswenson15: "testable javascript" author says lots of comments
ericswenson15: i d k
PlayITBruiser: never comment
OmarBeBallin: I like the fact he uses java
hardtarget4: qemu #1
ericswenson15: right!
ericswenson15: and they become wrong over time potentially?
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL
Ampalos23: # How this works???? --- BEST comment
PlayITBruiser: easier to read c than english
SlimEconomy: is the chair comfortable?
Hamled2: @georgehotz what would it take to do qira or usercorn-style dynamic analysis of a windows binary while running the tools on a linux host?
GenBurnside: one of you sub peeps should ask what his fav font is
PlayITBruiser: what sens u use
lightofhel1: PogChamp
ActionIsComing: its working now?
PlayITBruiser: is 1.3@400dpi ok
Ampalos23: Can this guy write a Hello World app?
alluxua: I subscribed on Jan, but geohot even did not twitch one.
spoco: the key to writing readable code is to not type it in python Kappa
billyera: !uptime
NonTrivial778: what's the best alternative of qira? Kappa
TwitchFoxy: notlikethis100 Learning so much just by sitting and listening here!
Reptilia0: daddr por like daddy
Zemulos: Zemulos subscribed at Tier 1.
PlayITBruiser: maybe do bbc
billyera: Just entered the stream. How are you Geo? plans for Spring break?
Ampalos23: How to download google?
ActionIsComing: just google it ^
Hamled2: I unfortunately missed all of that because someone was talking to me IRL :(
PlayITBruiser: can u illustrate in ms paint?
NonTrivial778: geohot is getting tired, he needs caffeine and ephedrine
Hamled2: @georgehotz what's the benefit of doing a userspace simulation with QEMU vs a full VM with like KVM or Xen
Hamled2: That makes a lot of sense. Is it also true that most of the time what you're analyzing doesn't "need" full emulation of a syscall?
okkessh: how do I subscribe
tybutnowyoudie: :(
Lazysloth: there is the sub button on top right
TwitchFoxy: @okkessh top right
revolutionist123: BibleThump
PlayITBruiser: pog
JumpTwiice: PogChamp
MrBankster: wat
Hamled2: I'm really excited for this! I started working recently on this Practical Binary Analysis https://nostarch.com/binaryanalysis
okkessh: top right is follow
Hamled2: *recently
nougekai: @georgehotz i'm a brain surgeon and this looks way complicated than what i'm doing :O
JumpTwiice: @Runner76 sure Kappa
nougekai: im serious
MrBankster: why is this guy so freakin hot
Hamled2: @georgehotz could you, eventually, add in some crazy shit like WINE to do windows binary emulation ontop of their emulated syscalls?
r1c1c: See you
JumpTwiice: that stuff about being a brain surgeon
r1c1c: !
PlayITBruiser: dream on
TwitchFoxy: See you
r1c1c: bye
tybutnowyoudie: bye
litesam: hEy
snapcs1: hey george HeyGuys
twiggy_io: What up homie
c252: hi
Chyeburashka: Chyeburashka subscribed with Twitch Prime.
fourhundredtwenty: jojo
c252: your hair is gone
snapcs1: get ready for the instagram sellout
ImAventus: Ayoo
jamesred2313: Sup Jew your computer is faster
ImAventus: Ads
shekel_gobblin: OK! Remember people, no talking about Comma.ai or logan paul's downfall or you will be banned from the 1mil instagram 2019 event. @georgehotz
dungeonmaster3: yo, what keyboard do you use
tiguent: damn ur a fast typer PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: What happened to hair?
ImAventus: Watch you doing writing a memoir
dorkmo: ouch
ShakDiesel: @georgehotz, what type of keyboard do you use?
tiguent: remove obs from scene
tanoshiizo: big hair best hair
Chyeburashka: Short logan paul
twiggy_io: @shakdiesel some Yamaha
Cube_Is_Life20: is Google trends the best way to measure success in this age?
guy_ross: how late am I?
snapcs1: 5 min
Chyeburashka: George doesn't love me, he didn't let me intern at comma when i was in high school
dorkmo: a chick flick
Chyeburashka: i cried every night for 3 months
ImAventus: Long geo
shekel_gobblin: I will pay $100 for a shirt on a merch store if you personally write twitchies on a shitty white tshirt with a marker
tiguent: google trends doesn't know who I am FeelsBadMan
jamesred2313: Why isn't it lagging
shekel_gobblin: 1 in chat if you want shitty white tshirt twitchies marker merch
erichtp: so many streams lately! loving it
dorkmo: taiwan #1
ddd_dota: @georgehotz suh dawg?
Chyeburashka: @erichtp my inner 9 year old is so excited (that's when i first discovered george)
twiggy_io: Taiwan server was better
Chyeburashka: We come for the memes, not the code
sfmoose: All of it
jamesred2313: 0%
Santiago_LHC: !insta
ImAventus: I thought this was sent channel lol jk
SkillzTech: None
fourhundredtwenty: 5%
tiguent: you might as well be speaking chinese, I have no idea what ur doing LUL
ImAventus: Amsr#
Manasoiu: whip nae nae
erichtp: channel your inner criminal #thugcrowd
ImAventus: Isn't this a ASMR channel??
SkillzTech: Jk like 3/10
lefse: What happend to the dx racer? xD
OArtero: are you using a topre keyboard?
va11as: hi :)
twiggy_io: No it’s a Yamaha keyboard. That’s why it’s white
shekel_gobblin: I will pay $100 for a shirt on a merch store if you personally write twitchies on a shitty white tshirt with a marker @georgehotz
erichtp: remember kids you can code as well as george if you sit in a dx racer
dorkmo: gotta pay extra for the black keys
va11as: do you review yc applications?
Santiago_LHC: Now we are ready for Fortnite!
Cube_Is_Life20: you need pewdiepie's chair
OArtero: are you using a topre keyboard?
tiguent: instagram DansGame
jamesred2313: 6000 to 10000?
Oivccomovai: holy smokes
jamesred2313: Buying followers
erichtp: 303 more followers til 10k PogChamp
ffthgezgxjkndd: who's botting followers
hAhamza: did you get a new mic?
Chyeburashka: @georgehotz why don't you read physics papers on streams, so that we can learn to break out of the simulation together
Cube_Is_Life20: I can bot him followers
erichtp: real followers only @Cube_Is_Life20
erichtp: no fakes allowed
Cube_Is_Life20: alrighty
tiguent: 50% of instagram accounts are bots
gusfrehse: hey
gusfrehse: nice hair
ffthgezgxjkndd: 75%
Chyeburashka: "The GMO people" im fucking dead
ImAventus: What happen to your blue check???🔥🔥🔥
Chyeburashka: How do we know global warming is real?
SparksCx: global warming is fake KKona
snapcs1: Cause its obvious
Chyeburashka: obvious != science
snapcs1: Oh wow really
Chyeburashka: yeah dude
Chyeburashka: believe it or not
snapcs1: Wow thats crazy
Chyeburashka: lol
jamesred2313: Global warming is good for the environment
Chyeburashka: oh shit
data_day_life: da fuc? 2 days in a row??
snapcs1: See theres proof right there
iamaflex: He keeps changing his tmux set up
HaywoodJabroni: hello @georgehotz HeyGuys
shekel_gobblin: @georgehotz some other hacker dude on twitch right now called you out, his username is @dowright, he wants a hack battle, but to rap
HaywoodJabroni: pajaS
data_day_life: LUL
Cube_Is_Life20: Windows version of qira, when?
davidsit_site: I regretted going irl midway thru earliers stream
luhartt: me
erichtp: rap battle ytcracker
davidsit_site: windows version of qira ever?
Cube_Is_Life20: probably never tbh
HaywoodJabroni: that will never happen
Oivccomovai: how was work at facebook?
davidsit_site: that was my guess and response to your initial question @cube_is_life20
Krazykarl037: is he hacking into the matrix?
jamesred2313: Hacking your mom
joker2k999: lol
twiggy_io: Toxic
abcdefghijklmopqrstuvwxyz: pytorch or tensorflow?
xfallenchamp: Hello my dear sirs
joker2k999: Dat ipython Tho
SparksCx: chat can you explain what he is doing, just briefly
dorkmo: he coding some stuff
SparksCx: i see
erichtp: you asked for brief u got brief
twiggy_io: He’s also reading some stuff
Oivccomovai: lol
joker2k999: porting Qemu to python3(linux)
dorkmo: yeah gotta read before you code
va11as: do you review yc applications?
SparksCx: yes
Cube_Is_Life20: damn python 3 syntax
joker2k999: yea. can't stand py3
grizvok: im late FUCK
erichtp: @grizvok its only 20 minutes into the stream
twiggy_io: Like 10 minutes
joker2k999: not too late bro
TH3KILLER321: Holy moly PogChamp
grizvok: oh damn, thought it started a while ago
Chyeburashka: Why is george writing ports instead jailbreaking the simulation?
Chyeburashka: *of
joker2k999: not today. its sunday.
Chyeburashka: lol
twiggy_io: Because it would break the simulation
dorkmo: gotta port to kill god
SparksCx: lol i remember his simulation talk LuL
Chyeburashka: after that talk im highkey worried about quantum computing
grizvok: in his church you dont break the simulation on sundays
Chyeburashka: understandable
joker2k999: after the talk you were? what about b4
Chyeburashka: didnt think about the cost to the simulator
dorkmo: just lowkey worried b4
Chyeburashka: so no, not before
Chyeburashka: lol
dungeonmaster3: Does anyone know what keyboard does george use ?
joker2k999: lol
twiggy_io: Yamaha
joker2k999: everyone asks that. Honda
dorkmo: 303
grizvok: i watched the first 30 minutes of the talk so far...pretty interesting
SparksCx: just import a keyboard
joker2k999: I don't know bro.
joker2k999: its the one w/ no text. idk the name
dorkmo: Roland keyboard
Chyeburashka: im still sad george doesnt think DMT will help us break out at all
Chyeburashka: but he knows more than me, so..
erichtp: getting his keyboard dont mean you gonna type faster just get what you like lmfao
luhartt: sudo make me a sandwich
abcdefghijklmopqrstuvwxyz: tensorflow or pytorch?
joker2k999: dmt is the poor mans j/b the sim solution
use_after_free: damn didnt know you streamed PogChamp
ABuffSeagull: btw, the new thing in python 3 is to use f strings, so it would just be print(f"entry point: ")
erichtp: @joker2k999 crack is the way to punch up
joker2k999: I would use tensor flow. keras.
joker2k999: @luhartt you're not root.,
Chyeburashka: @joker2k999 "the poor man's JB" love it
puffnfresh: write more Coq
Chyeburashka: this chat is golden
Chyeburashka: coolest group of twitch nerds
Keyeh: hello geo and chat HeyGuys
dorkmo: sup bru
Keyeh: what u working on
mxd8: <3
davidsit_site: thank you and hello. qira
Chyeburashka: porting QEMU to python3 @Keyeh
dorkmo: writing a program from flour and eggs
Chyeburashka: hot
dorkmo: and a little milk and butter
Chyeburashka: come on dorkmo i can only get so wet
puffnfresh: more Coq plz
Chyeburashka: IM SORRY
Chyeburashka: I LOVE YOU GEORGE
joker2k999: really?
puffnfresh: need some of that formally verified software
BigGucciGuap: herro
Keyeh: ty for the info guys Kappa
joker2k999: ok. so. idk wtf we're doing bro's. can't late. lol
Cube_Is_Life20: he's porting twilight?
joker2k999: *came
Chyeburashka: I love that george has "tutorial for python language pulled up"
dorkmo: the whole twilight saga
davidsit_site: no blue checkmark on Twitter. not verified code
Chyeburashka: damn david, brutal
joker2k999: LOL
abcdefghijklmopqrstuvwxyz: @georgehotz tensorflow or pytorch?
puffnfresh: oh no @davidsit_site
Oivccomovai: nobody can understand geniuses
va11as: @georgehotz do you review YC applications?
joker2k999: only geniuses understand genius
Chyeburashka: So if we understand the stream we are geniuses?
Chyeburashka: shit, better tell my math teacher
davidsit_site: id10ts
davidsit_site: or pebkac's
va11as: lol
Oivccomovai: we should change the "subscribe to pewdiepiew" thing to "follow geohot on instagram"
ffthgezgxjkndd: great music choices
SparksCx: ummm ok
Keyeh: yeah LUL
Cube_Is_Life20: @oivccomovai the printer hack?
Keyeh: its just the same riff but sped up
joker2k999: i think he has something planned that will get him to that 1mill followers.
abcdefghijklmopqrstuvwxyz: @georgehotz tensorflow or pytorch?
Chyeburashka: @joker2k999 openpilot 6
Oivccomovai: @Cube_Is_Life20 yes
joker2k999: we don't we about that stuff not he stream
joker2k999: LOL. got u
SparksCx: lol
luhartt: keras tho
joker2k999: i concur
Cube_Is_Life20: I have an AA meeting to go to, I'll be back if he's still live in 2 hours
use_after_free: you should add the tag 'science & technology' to your stream, thats where programming streams usually are
Keyeh: he's typing the same rhythm of the song Pog
dorkmo: #english
Oivccomovai: thats not basic
use_after_free: gl @Cube_Is_Life20
dungeonmaster3: what is even going on.
dorkmo: do you really want to exit? (y/n)
Chyeburashka: y
use_after_free: %n
SparksCx: o
searchingforlife: @georgehotz why import print_function in python3?
twiggy_io: Backwards compatibility
Keyeh: is he writting another debugger?
Keyeh: @georgehotz were u an emo in the 2000's?
dorkmo: thats a subscriber questions bro
Keyeh: i'll try my chances
Keyeh: lmao
twiggy_io: 100% subscriber question.
use_after_free: (subscriber): Keepo
Keyeh: i might subscribe if he answers, does that count Kappa
joker2k999: what cool revEEGR tools are hot in them streets these days?
TonsUhFun: ghidra?
Chyeburashka: @Keyeh i gotchu
Chyeburashka: @georgehotz were u an emo in the 2000's?
joker2k999: omg.. isn't that bricking os's lol
Chyeburashka: ghidira?
lukihker: twitch did'n save videos that some weeks ago?i can't find the previous videos
dorkmo: check youtube
joker2k999: sup w/ some chill code music?
lukihker: all right
Caene: No lag today?
HaywoodJabroni: pajaShrugL forsenE pajaShrugR
twiggy_io: Taiwan server
glitchedoutt: global warming?
joker2k999: immmm....
dorkmo: not me :/
HaywoodJabroni: D: no
joker2k999: not?
joker2k999: call
Keyeh: a function doesn't exist?
stephenhuh: call a fn
HaywoodJabroni: calls stuff
bboc_kz: Seems to me like the write is unmapped, but I've just tuned in so what do i know Kappa
use_after_free: unwinds stack?
joker2k999: pulls men from a register
data_day_life: it gitz $ from the data bus
satire_: save registers to the stack
satire_: jumps to the function
Keyeh: PogChamp chat
ScrubLifeChoseMe: POGGERS
HaywoodJabroni: PogChamp @satire_
ScrubLifeChoseMe: PogChamp
use_after_free: Pog
bboc_kz: PogChamp
knilecrack: I thoughtt it calls from stack
youngsachi: Pogchamp
joker2k999: PogChamp
use_after_free: it pushes args on stack and then jumps to the mem addr right?
glitchedoutt: it can't write to the registers?
t_lokus: just got here, something to do with c calling standard? maybe?
Keyeh: we learnin'
use_after_free: were pleb twitch chatters we know nothing
AnAnonymousGifter: An anonymous user gifted a Tier 1 sub to satire_!
use_after_free: PogChamp
HaywoodJabroni: PogChamp @satire_
Keyeh: anonymous PogChamp
Cctrio: So you can explain what you are doing :)
joker2k999: to learnz bro
use_after_free: to learn shit like this? :p
ScrubLifeChoseMe: gotta start somewhere george :)
joker2k999: but we gotta watch it back on 1/8 the speed. lol
Oivccomovai: i'm just a fan of yours, sir
Oivccomovai: sorry
lostchange: I enjoy your thought process
Caene: I feel useless FeelsBadMan
Caene: Why am I here
joker2k999: most are prolly here for the church. lol
use_after_free: why are we here PepeHands
ScrubLifeChoseMe: clout
dorkmo: i feel like i just came into class and didnt do the homework
HaywoodJabroni: @dorkmo LuL
HyperSpectral: LUL @dorkmo
joker2k999: LOL
Caene: We should all read off of satire_'s notes LUL
use_after_free: true LUL
a_cetologist: a_cetologist subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ABuffSeagull: does ipython not have a reload file functionality? 🤔
HaywoodJabroni: forsenPrime
HaywoodJabroni: not me :D
bboc_kz: will this be on this quiz?
joker2k999: eof?
Caene: I know the answer guys, whisper me for my paypal info. Kappa
knilecrack: so is it a call stack on the end?
funcionario_net: !uptime
HaywoodJabroni: pajaS
joker2k999: overflow bro.
r1c1c: can anyone please gift me a sub, i'll be grateful eternally :)
Caene: I hate gifts DansGame
Caene: You should to
knilecrack: you are praying in wrong church @r1c1c
funcionario_net: !commands
Sandoww: what do you think about Jon Blow and his Jai programming language?
use_after_free: explain more
TonsUhFun: dude ur on another level
dorkmo: something about adding some tags to the pirntout?
Keyeh: chat is Pepega
HaywoodJabroni: pajaGa
joker2k999: loading
use_after_free: creates a stack
Caene: He's teaching PogChamp
HaywoodJabroni: PogChamp
HaywoodJabroni: NotLikeThis
thedavosfinger: Is this basic programming??shieett man,i only understand pritn()...XD
dorkmo: lol same
joker2k999: creating a lib?
dorkmo: load the stack into unicorn
Keyeh: this basic assembly programming bro
HaywoodJabroni: hes doin some crazy shit in python
thedavosfinger: is this python?
HaywoodJabroni: @thedavosfinger yea
thedavosfinger: nice
redbullwiiings: We live in a society. Don't be sheep. Always evolve. Grow. Learn. Don't sit here watching somebody else if its not helping you in anyway. Distractions are constantly being designed by for the NWO. The more distractions the less worry about a crippling government. Please teach yourselves the human mind is capable of so much more.
dorkmo: F
HaywoodJabroni: qira seems pretty awesome
wltrz: what keyboard do you use?
dorkmo: bro
Caene: @redbullwiiings 2longdidntread can you make your words into a meme gif instead?
geobitz: you gonna use qira with tesla?
use_after_free: stupid question, doesnt he need to encode your stack in little endian?
Keyeh: @redbullwiiings is this a copypasta?
Caene: Kappa
thedavosfinger: it sounds like a mechanic keyboard
use_after_free: like add a < before QQQQQ
bboc_kz: is this a python web app?
glitchedoutt: He will ban you if you ask any questions about his keyboard
joker2k999: are we making a linker file
use_after_free: i thouight <Q was little endian
Zipzipcekirge: corrupted stack oh no
use_after_free: maybe the default is lil endian
use_after_free: good rapper name
esence: what is this project he's working on, is it similar to IDA-Pro?
뚱인디요: It's so nice that u r streaming often these days
satire_: isnt that stuff from the kernel
satire_: or libc
Countolafs: whats a stack?
ABuffSeagull: this is making me want to fire up a Zachtronics game
GameMe: What is he writing?
뚱인디요: NO
use_after_free: ELF FeelsGoodMan
Keyeh: no
TonsUhFun: this is all wizard shit
뚱인디요: honestly, i watch ur stream all the time, but i don't get a single thing
joker2k999: sounds familiar
thedavosfinger: ez pc
뚱인디요: he makes me wanna buy mac
use_after_free: PogChamp
Keyeh: EZ
bboc_kz: PogChamp FIRST TRY
ABuffSeagull: working PogChamp
thezilion: finally
Countolafs: ez
youngsachi: PogChamp
use_after_free: i barely understand it
Keyeh: its cool as fuck tho
Caene: @georgehotz you want us to leave?
Caene: FeelsBadMan
use_after_free: not everyone knows how binaries work, let alone reversing them @georgehotz believe it or not its pretty hard for us normies LUL
뚱인디요: Is there like a tip when u get stuck?
knilecrack: where is the result from syscall?
ABuffSeagull: Oh boy, now my operating systems class will actually come in handy. I know syscalls!
knilecrack: or can you trace it?
뚱인디요: Like when i code, i get stuck and it takes me DAYS to figure out how to fix it but u just somehow magically fixes it in like 3 min
use_after_free: VoteYea
Irkanu: Subs are immune right? bogaDeal
knilecrack: when you call kernel to do stuff
geobitz: jaja
joker2k999: call to the systools.
knilecrack: rofl
joker2k999: lol
thedavosfinger: syscall is someting that calls the system..rigth??
Zipzipcekirge: low level os functions
ABuffSeagull: Goes into a protected mode and runs some system code, or something like that
joker2k999: yes subs are good.
glitchedoutt: it's a set of calls provided by the kernel to do some basic shit
use_after_free: context switch kernel function call
knilecrack: or low lvl OS functions yes
1garo: !uptime
satire_: syscall will take whatever is in eax as argument/code to know which syscall to make right before it traps
bboc_kz: syscall calls some internal code in the kernel
akbang47: yo bro do even the the piano u pleb
뚱인디요: which ide is he using atm?
joker2k999: so were not linking qira to a web-app?
ABuffSeagull: so with this unicorn engine, are you trying to run a program just straight on the processor, with no OS/kernel?
esence: hey why don't you use Ruby for this type of stuff
ABuffSeagull: "processor" being the emulator
joker2k999: idk about unicorn
thedavosfinger: @georgehotz are you god of programming?
Zipzipcekirge: which architecture is emulated
esence: install gentoo
use_after_free: x86-64 im pretty sure @Zipzipcekirge
ABuffSeagull: but still no OS/Kernel, I'm guessing, which is really cool
뚱인디요: i wish i can take his brain and migrate it to mine
joker2k999: yup
akbang47: put ur hours in
mikeyyinspace: Jailbreaking the Simulation with George Hotz
PapaDukie: so qira gives you the assembly code and then you run that through unicorn?
ABuffSeagull: also, apparently the new hot thing for python is pipenv, which is a mixture of pip and virtualenv, and allows you to locally download and run python libraries
TonsUhFun: yeah ask george how much time he has spent using assembly.... probably a long fcknnnn time.. its not magic but hard fcknn work
akbang47: is that really a new hot thing tho
Sandoww: 2 space indentation? are you a sociopath?
ABuffSeagull: locally meaning for just that project, and not have to install it system wide with pip
Infinitelym: ooh haircut
carty711: I am so bad at reverse engineering. would you suggest practicing programming in assembly to get used to it or just continue doing reverse engineering stuff?
joker2k999: gdb
ballen_7: what is qira
joker2k999: a debugger
MorbidlyBrobese: Did @georgehotz become an Instagram model yet?
bboc_kz: wait qira saves the state of every register through every instruction?
bboc_kz: MonkaS
risky_banana: notlikethis100 @georgehotz I just watched "Jailbreaking the Simulation" and now I'm I've lost motivation for the day... WHY YOU DO THIS TO ME
risky_banana: coding
joker2k999: rant incoming?
ballen_7: what is qira for
BallEm: Mergence baby!
risky_banana: just my day job haha
use_after_free: whats the tl;dw of that @risky_banana
akbang47: could you summarize the thesis of that talk
alluxua: Machine learning for trading stocks. I am in
risky_banana: @use_after_free there is no tl;dr go watch it
joker2k999: no day job is cool. lol
use_after_free: thats a thing already @alluxua lol
Keyeh: mumbling in quantum mechanics language
risky_banana: @georgehotz I'm refractoring legacy PHP.... so yeah, nah... I dunno... I need to come up with a new project :)
wigginsfan22: how was your day george
cIvIcbooks: u ever read nick bostrom?
alluxua: I am a robot while doing my day job
P0LY: LUL
knilecrack: delete instsagram
Zipzipcekirge: im using javascript for senior project. shittiest language probably
use_after_free: is it about a privesc/jailbreak in actual physics?
risky_banana: @georgehotz well.... anyway, I liked your chat dude, got me thinking
use_after_free: i know thats been theorized before
slimydude: road to 10k
risky_banana: :)
knilecrack: rofl
joker2k999: lol.
alluxua: Gosh,that picture is so funny
hexicity1: hexicity1 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
acheesedanish00: 4 streams
acheesedanish00: wowe
thedavosfinger: @georgehotz georgehotz VS pewdiepie
joker2k999: your streams are lit bro
dorkmo: punch up
risky_banana: risky_banana subscribed at Tier 1.
akbang47: LMAO
knilecrack: :D
TonsUhFun: LUL
knilecrack: lets go
ziggyzergling: LUL
youngsachi: PogChamp
risky_banana: the riskiest banana
BallEm: PogChamp
joker2k999: lol bastards
JustAnEdtior: Do you think you will ever do CTF streams?
hexicity1: Hey George, i sent you a message on discord, is that a place to reach you viably? don't read it on stream just have a burning question for you.
joker2k999: i guess gamers do Mountain dew and coders do spinDrift
Zipzipcekirge: do you take pentest contracts?
alluxua: I want to make a million and give to someone I love. I donot need money at all
risky_banana: almost always no
bboc_kz: you're no longer working with comma ai?
joker2k999: help
joker2k999: (assistance)
TonsUhFun: difference is how they spend their time
risky_banana: if you earned the 1mil, then you're likely going to deploy it better than someone you're just giving it away to
bboc_kz: Well you can't purely make investments, a man's gotta eat!
tohsdnilb: Hookers and blow
alluxua: I just want to give my parents. They can count cash at home
wigginsfan22: what keyboard do u use
davidsit_site: I'm having a bad week. this conversation is a surprising pick me up
P0LY: lottery winners going broke?
hexicity1: I'd be more than happy coming on periscope with you. That would be a great opportunity to me. Is there any chance of setting that up sometime? I'm sick at the minute so won't bother you today, but is that something possible?
risky_banana: but hookers and blow are a staple in my diet ?
hexicity1: ohh, i see, apologies
grizvok: LOL burn
alluxua: Counting cash at home make my parents happy
P0LY: D:
davidsit_site: lol
BallEm: Boon
BallEm: Boom*
hexicity1: i was under the impression periscope was group calling, somewhat like skype
JustAnEdtior: Do you think you will ever do CTF streams?
risky_banana: @georgehotz did you watch the HBO show Silicon Valley
risky_banana: it's the best
davidsit_site: that's his life
Zipzipcekirge: you can chat using discord
Keyeh: @risky_banana i like that show too
Dieun: Hello!
k_peen: discord
alluxua: Did you guys call hookers? Just curious
risky_banana: rofl
JustAnEdtior: Do you think you will ever do CTF streams?
knilecrack: never pay for hookers
knilecrack: pussy and water always come for free
AzazelTheGoat: do you still drink that fancy tea beverage?
tohsdnilb: That's what the blow is for...
alluxua: Well, you got to pay for water
P0LY: is tea good for longevity?
risky_banana: is the sky blue
grizvok: yes tea will make you live significantly longer
cosmoz_AI: probably already answered this but why mac ?
risky_banana: WHO CARES ABOUT YOUR TEA, WE ARE LIVING IN A SIMULATION
grizvok: Kappa
davidsit_site: what about an idea that works in small form (and is a self sustaining business) but you can't yet scale hardware wise due to up front manufacturing costs?
dorkmo: pure leaf tea makes you live the longest
ethbow: why is 1080p the only quality option?
alluxua: Hey, hey, dorkmo
dorkmo: hey hey
grizvok: @davidsit_site i'd consider that a successful implementation
P0LY: I think you need to be a partner to get quality options
davidsit_site: me too. that's why I have two jobs
BallEm: Who's code is that?
AzazelTheGoat: whose drink is that
davidsit_site: but they were talking about money from other people. something that seems magical
carty711: carty711 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
use_after_free: 10 mins into the jailbreaking the simulation and i wonder if youve ever heard of agnosticism lol @georgehotz
davidsit_site: yes.
PapaDukie: @davidsit_site kickstarter
davidsit_site: thank you
Keyeh: its Pepega topic
Caene: Thank God for that.
hexicity1: Well if you don't mind me asking here: I am currently 20, at UK university doing Compsci with AI. I do a lot of data science work, in either hackathons or trying to get into Kaggle competitions. My question is essentially what advice would you give, or what steps would you take in my shoes, to get to a position that I can hand a CV in to yourself in 3 years time when I am finished university, and come to the states to work for you specifically, especially in the instance that Comma.ai is still a
AzazelTheGoat: AzazelTheGoat subscribed with Twitch Prime.
data_day_life: don't forget to ban keyboard questions
grizvok: yeah kb questions must die
AzazelTheGoat: take my twitch prime sub. you've earned it
bboc_kz: Kickstarter is a pretty efficient way to watch bad ideas flop and good ideas get stolen before enough capital is raised to bring it to market by the inventors
bboc_kz: 🤷
P0LY: smart juicers are the future 4Head
Keyeh: @hexicity1 asking for a job much
AzazelTheGoat: I want to know the name of that tea he drinks. it's the secret to his power
Zipzipcekirge: i think kickstarter is better for like almost finished products
data_day_life: LUL
hexicity1: @Keyeh im not in a position to ask for a job, thats part of the point of the question
th3_maj0r: hi guys
PapaDukie: kickstarter is good for board game ideas
dev12341: !keyboard OpieOP
aamiiiiii: aamiiiiii subscribed with Twitch Prime.
hexicity1: I want to be in a position to ask for a job, in 3 years time
tohsdnilb: No show some initiative
Phantomhive_: dude u dont even know what youll want in 3 years
tohsdnilb: Do stuff now
Keyeh: by the way elon has a nice video about that
tohsdnilb: People of earth are not patient
Irkanu: Yeah... I couldn't have imagined I'd be where I am today 3 years ago.
HyperSpectral: HyperSpectral subscribed with Twitch Prime.
hexicity1: i'm doing a lot now - atleast i feel, and its great. I'm doing a lot of software work for local companies while i'm at university and generally building my CV
joseya7: Are there any chances that you could stream basic programming for beginners?
grizvok: that isn't something he'd ever do...i think
AzazelTheGoat: I don't think he's got time for that.
un3okapi: @joseya7 does he look like a casual to you?
Zipzipcekirge: he wont stream something he already knows thats for sure
grizvok: there are so many places online already
tohsdnilb: That keyboard does not have a slow speed
hexicity1: but from people who have that experience, and look back, theres always a 'i would have done this' answer, I was hoping for something along those lines of this is what i would do in that position
Phantomhive_: idk go to some big company leak their source code then ask for a job from george
AzazelTheGoat: anyone got any opinions on the "powershell in a month of lunches" book?
hexicity1: definitely a naive question, so I apologies for the lack of initiative
tcsiwula: I c dead unicorns
Keyeh: @hexicity1 you said something about competing, what do you compete on?
un3okapi: @hexicity1 stop talking about it in twitch chat. Just send it in 3 years and follow up with taht.
aamiiiiii: Even when he does basic programming im still hella confused about whats going on but that most likely bc im only in my 3rd year of university comp sci
tohsdnilb: Think global not local
use_after_free: i just realized 'exploiting natures kernel and do a privesc to escape the simulation' is actually a valid explanaition for the fermi paradox
hexicity1: @Keyeh done a lot with Hackathons recently, locally with uni and have signed up for a couple more locally. I have been using Kaggle recently for competitions, but more just for my ownsake, haven't competed in it yet
tcsiwula: Did you hear a keyboard?
Keyeh: @hexicity1 so competitive programming or just data science stuff?
alluxua: Crack leetcode. You can get any job
aamiiiiii: can anyone give a tldr of what hes doing, just joined in :)
tcsiwula: rm -rf /
dorkmo: special ASMR keyboard keys
hexicity1: @Keyeh more data science, I wouldn't fully say thats a path I chose myself, its just where I have found the most opportunity in my area
Keyeh: @hexicity1 cool
tcsiwula: while !hungry kitty.sleep
alluxua: ML in stock trading. Then you donot need a job
hexicity1: time to invest in Bitcoin and retire i think
tcsiwula: Ya ml 401k get on it
alluxua: Yeah, I figured out how to invest in crypto. Paid some tuitions as well
P0LY: a couple years late there bud Kappa
hexicity1: @Phantomhive_ where do i know your name from btw?
Infinitelym: you read really fast
Mendacii_: You are my inspiration to learn how to code
tcsiwula: mu.mmap(&khole)
aamiiiiii: georgie didn't go to university right?
tcsiwula: rm -rm /
alluxua: I think he finished CMU
tcsiwula: rm -rm / .
tcsiwula: rm -rm
tcsiwula: rm -rm /
tcsiwula: Hahahaha
tcsiwula: while bankaccount < rent; type
aamiiiiii: wait like carnegie mellon university or central Michigan
blizz191: 1m2019.com
joker2k999: George be like “I can’t believe you guys don’t know how dual quantum save states work..” lol
davidsit_site: lol
tcsiwula: Core dump ur mom
th3_maj0r: rude
P0LY: what was that?
tcsiwula: jp jp all
tcsiwula: One love
aamiiiiii: Did any of you guys struggle with Calculus at university?
tcsiwula: Import
aamiiiiii: Programming no big deal but I cant fucking pass a calc class with more than a C- to save my life
tcsiwula: I failed calc three times
davidsit_site: ....
aamiiiiii: oof
dorkmo: same
dorkmo: i gave up lol
tcsiwula: Flush buffer
alluxua: You gave up what, dorkmo?
dorkmo: calculus
blizz191: calc 2 is death
hexicity1: how come he shaved the beard?
aamiiiiii: my friend is way more talented at coding than any of our friends in CS but he struggles with calc the most to the point where he might be on academic probation
tcsiwula: Seg fault
tcsiwula: You have been warned;)
aamiiiiii: im in calc 2 rn for the second time and its still ass
alluxua: Damn it, you guys should make friends with me earlier. I got 99 of all math classes ....
dorkmo: i feel like coding uses the creative writing part of the brain more than the math side sometimes
tcsiwula: lol jit in python wahooooieeeeee
aamiiiiii: I was expecting physics to suck because everyone said it was, but it was fine
litesam: !UPTIME
joker2k999: lol
dorkmo: 0000 0000 0000 0000
joker2k999: stack is suspect
litesam: @joker2k999 !uptime
aamiiiiii: is he still porting qira to python 3?
blizz191: aaa,o;;;o
aamiiiiii: is that what this is
davidsit_site: yes
tcsiwula: Ahahahaha
tcsiwula: Seg whore
aamiiiiii: what was it before
joker2k999: he said he wasn't.
Keyeh: he's doing something with unicorn
blizz191: @aamiiiiii dude same in calc2 again and in physics right now
joker2k999: idk...
blizz191: my physics proff is a fucking troll, test are two questions that combine like 6 chapters into one question
davidsit_site: wow
JonThomasK: stuff is good
aamiiiiii: oof
joker2k999: i thought we was linking qira to some web app.....
blizz191: like incline slop with friction, spring and collision in one question
hardtarget4: Stuff PogChamp
grizvok: that's what she said
aamiiiiii: is it physics 1 or 2
tcsiwula: Rwx ftw
Keyeh: @blizz191 had a lot of those in the math dep, so many trolls
aamiiiiii: oh so 1
joker2k999: physics was a bitch
aamiiiiii: luckily I did fine in physics, helped cushin the blow form calc 2
joker2k999: eegrPhysics.
blizz191: dude legit says all forces are equal and opposite but the curve is sure as hell not equal to the force downwards applied to my grade by the tests
aamiiiiii: I wonder if George passed those classes with his eyes closed if he went to university
alluxua: I will get the same keyboard. The sound of the keyboard calms me down.
joker2k999: lol
blizz191: I could see George getting hyped with philosophy classes or something
grizvok: LOL
joker2k999: he's in the club.
aamiiiiii: Hey i just subbed a bit ago
dev12341: monkaS
hexicity1: I want the CherryMx' Geohot's
blizz191: l0l
aamiiiiii: All good;) keep doing you big man
joker2k999: LOL
dev12341: PepeHands
metrix84: !uptime
aamiiiiii: I cant understand a single thing he is doing. What is qira
akaEcho: @aamiiiiii you aren't alone
joker2k999: a debugger bro.
Countolafs: a debugger of what?
alluxua: I am sorry I didnot realize keyboard is a banned word. Will not say it any more
Keyeh: k word monkaS
hardtarget4: basically a 'time traveling' debugger that he did years ago at google. Microsoft just now put this kind of functionality in windbg preview
aamiiiiii: for python or for anything, because I saw him running it on C code for the font hack
alluxua: I donot understand what he is coding, but think it is pretty cool
BallEm: Im just soaking and absorbing
aamiiiiii: interesting does that mean it logs all tests so you can see everything to debug code form the past
shtaken6939: its assembly on that right?
blizz191: why is he not using tmux anymore and is using screen?
joker2k999: its like gbd but can go in rev back up the stack
Keyeh: he is using tmux though
aamiiiiii: i think this is explaining what he is doing, makes a little sense
aamiiiiii: https://blog.ret2.io/2018/06/19/pwn2own-2018-root-cause-analysis/
blizz191: thats his screenrc tho? did he change his stmux.conf to look like screen? I think he is using screen tbh
Keyeh: one of his repos is called configuration, you might want to look into it
th3_maj0r: it's screen
blizz191: maybe its causes he is sshed in somewhere
joker2k999: into ubuntu.
th3_maj0r: yep
blizz191: aw
aamiiiiii: does anyone else here code in the terminal or is george just pro strat level
th3_maj0r: he code in vim
joker2k999: i do.
joker2k999: emacs ftw
grizvok: i do a little when ssh'd into my server but typically no
yeet20042: I code in pycharm
alluxua: It is a shame. I code in Jupyter notebook
blizz191: @aamiiiiii VIM only
yeet20042: But George codes in vim I think
yeet20042: I’m also very new
alluxua: It seems coding in Jupypter notebook got discriminated
carty711: do you have sublime open for just looking over other code?
litesam: @georgehotz you are neare 10,000 followers in instagram. Any special announcement then!!
joker2k999: yea.. its purrrdy.
shtaken6939: can someone tell us what need to learn to code like that xd
grizvok: a fuck ton.
blizz191: I use sublime if I am looking at a huge file and I want to be able to scroll through it quickly to get a feel, but writing my own code always vim
alluxua: Like what? Like geohot coding?
joker2k999: i don't think you learn to code like that bro
yeet20042: Basically coding out of the womb than doing it for how ever many years old George is
blizz191: The best part of watching george code is you know like 10% of what hes doing
joker2k999: thats why you gotta play it back at 1/8 the speed like me bro
yeet20042: Is George working on qira?
blizz191: @joker2k999 LOL thats the way to do it
aamiiiiii: wait so are you guys mainly programming in python?
aamiiiiii: for VIM
alluxua: Geohot started coding about 10 years old. And then his brain got used to the coding
shtaken6939: well if i would just understand what is he doing
joker2k999: i watch other code streams. is NOT the same.
blizz191: I use vim to code in python yes
joker2k999: but, I'm basically here for the rants. lol
blizz191: bin is the same as tab tab on a mac
shtaken6939: and why doesnt programers stream theres no streamer
grizvok: people stream programming quite a bit
joker2k999: yup.
grizvok: always at least a couple of people programming
blizz191: Not the same as george tho
joker2k999: its school season. summer tryna find a stream is a bitch...
blizz191: most mere mortals who stream programming have to think and research stuff, george just does it
dorkmo: george is the HBO premium movie package of coding streams
playfiendss: @georgehotz PogChamp How are you? What are we making?
aamiiiiii: Debugging just seems like a bitch without an IDE
aamiiiiii: I havent reached that level yet
grizvok: the kind of stuff he is debugging isn't going to be found with an ide
aamiiiiii: trueee
blizz191: hed have to debug the debugger to get the debugger to work
aamiiiiii: Xtreme coding is what they call it in the industry I believe
davidsit_site: did that earlier
Rottifanboy15: !uptime
ivylions: whats this dude sippin on
blizz191: tea?
dorkmo: spin drift water
dorkmo: brought to you by
aamiiiiii: do you guys prefer python over java? I have yet to touch python and am wondering if I should start
joker2k999: all his functions are custom, and kinda funny
blizz191: no tea sponser?
dorkmo: oh nvm
alluxua: Pure leaf tea
aamiiiiii: rather than sticking to java
th3_maj0r: ahahahaah
dorkmo: generic noname water
joker2k999: LOL. SoBs
davidsit_site: nice
IAmABeautifulButterfly: Just tuned in, what are you trying to build/fix for qira?
blizz191: they probably wanted to collaborate and not give free shit huh
yeet20042: I only know python but it works for like eveything
alluxua: Bro, just drink tap water. Save money. No chemicals
joker2k999: lol
VisionHeavy: plenty of chemicals in tap water
dorkmo: flouride
yeet20042: So I feel like it would be helpful to learn @aamiiiiii
blizz191: lol flouride big prob in utah right now
grizvok: if you are learning programming and have worked with java for a while it's probably not beneficial to switch
VisionHeavy: also chlorine
alluxua: Boil the water
aamiiiiii: Doesn't he live in LA where the chemicals outnumber the H2O in the tap water
joker2k999: uh huh... no. don't drink tap. we facility good health around here. lol
grizvok: if you are ready to learn a new language then yeah python is awesome
Quad___lol: EU tap water is fine
aamiiiiii: that makes sense! @grizvok
shtaken6939: bro is there any project based python tutorials?
blizz191: like a million
joker2k999: theres a bunch of good code camps are good but are crazy $$$
grizvok: you don't need to bootcamp to learn
shtaken6939: any link?
Rottifanboy15: holy shit these walls of texts
aamiiiiii: I struggle a lot coming up with projects to do on my own other than the ones I get assigned at university.
Quad___lol: i decided to learn chinese since its not object oriented nor functional
davidsit_site: lol
shtaken6939: ha ha
ivylions: you're gonna need to learn to search for your self my dude
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii I have some projects in mind but never have the time nor the partner to work with
dorkmo: watch how george uses google
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii whats your tech stack?
shtaken6939: @ivylions ik
alluxua: I can teach you Chinese. $50/ hour
joker2k999: lol good rate.
davidsit_site: no. ps3 please
Quad___lol: @alluxua i can teach you programming 100/h
davidsit_site: py3
dorkmo: i can teach openscad 10/hr
grizvok: @dorkmo indeed. even though a lot of the stuff he does is difficult to understand the way he goes about implementing the stuff is invaluable.
alluxua: Probably I code better
shtaken6939: @Quad___lol xd
blizz191: I will teach scratch for 10$ an hour
Quad___lol: or modern art for 150$
IAmABeautifulButterfly: #include <sys/syscall.h>
shtaken6939: no war in chat please
aamiiiiii: @Rottifanboy15 java and c
davidsit_site: @alluxua. you both should do a qira search module across memory nodes and see whose is more maintainable by George
aamiiiiii: @Rottifanboy15 what about you
Quad___lol: i decided to teach my girlfriend C and i think we gonna break up after the next lesson
aamiiiiii: hahahha
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii i do RoR, React/React Native, Node
blizz191: L0l
shtaken6939: @Rottifanboy15 web
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii you should learn up on those frameworks/libraries
cryptoguys: why not use gitkraken its actually insane @georgehotz
joker2k999: damn. we had one job.
data_day_life: we did it chat!
blizz191: @aamiiiiii if you know java and c you would be fine doing anything in python
Quad___lol: gitkraken is good since all i work on is non commercial Kappa
blizz191: @IAmABeautifulButterfly This guy
alluxua: Lol, are you serious to teach girlfriend c ?
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii but in college I only do Java
anatoly1974: nice haircut @georgehotz
Quad___lol: @alluxua ye, she wanted to learn programming so lets start from the hardest one to th easiest one lmao
tauzN: BlessRNG
blizz191: @Quad___lol ya you about to be single
aamiiiiii: @Rottifanboy15 Yeah im in college right now and it has only been java and C and I have not gotten around to other languages and they have not entered any frameworks yet
alluxua: Teach her CSS. Girls like CSS
z0di4ckx: hey
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii they are not gonna teach you any frameworks. You've got to learn them yourselves
davidsit_site: @aamiiiiii self educate
shtaken6939: @alluxua thats for sure
cryptoguys: don't limit your programming to college thats the worst thing you could ever do
Rottifanboy15: @aamiiiiii i bet while you are learning these frameworks, ideas will come to you
Quad___lol: she is actually really good at math and logical thinking (yes she is a girl and can be as random as PHP - the only deterministic thing in PHP is a random number generator)
grizvok: Learning C is going to do more for a programmer than learning react imo
aamiiiiii: true thats why i am trying to come up with projects to do
joker2k999: yea C is legit.
sen_lala: can you shrink the terminal please, you are covering the code
blizz191: @aamiiiiii go make a web scraper to scrape the billboard top 100 songs, then download them from youtube, you will learn a little about scraping, html requests and ffmpeg
shtaken6939: @Quad___lol is php bad bro?
cryptoguys: React is just a framework in JS correct?
Rottifanboy15: @grizvok we are already learning C and Java in college so
aamiiiiii: thats a good project idea!
shtaken6939: @blizz191 nc idea pro
Rottifanboy15: React is more a library than a framework
aamiiiiii: ill save that rn
Quad___lol: @shtaken6939 of course not! PHP is amazing if you want to be discriminated
alluxua: Do you guys leetcode?
blizz191: How i got music to play on my linux device cause no apple music
Quad___lol: languages are like races IRL, there will always be racism
Quad___lol: and PHP is the subhuman race
cryptoguys: Use any language for the right job man
cryptoguys: thats all you can do
cryptoguys: not sure why people shit on certain languages
StopitDonk: @georgehotz if you really want to learn how to program..?? im interested...
shtaken6939: @Quad___lol ha ha
cryptoguys: apparently smallTalk was supposed to be the best language
cryptoguys: yo hotz what's your thoughts on smalltalk
davidsit_site: I got a lisp
aamiiiiii: @georgehotz if you really want to learn how to program..?? im interested... RT
dorkmo: english is the best language
shtaken6939: @StopitDonk will u teach us xd
tea_em_oh_six: i gained iq points when i followed you on instagram
StopitDonk: please finish your sentence @georgehotz
davidsit_site: @stopitdonk @georgehotz repeat with subscriber status
IAmABeautifulButterfly: @georgehotz can you make your camera view slightly smaller so we can read the full vim view
cryptoguys: his camera is way too big i'd agree.
grizvok: @Rottifanboy15 I'm definitely not hating on React. Best UI library every built.
asianboychris: @georgehotz what keyboard are you using?
dorkmo: the sponsors need to have the clear product placement
joker2k999: he's in the zone.
grizvok: @Rottifanboy15 ever*
Rottifanboy15: @grizvok lol its Facebook's man
joker2k999: it takes me at least two l-theanin b4 i get there.
grizvok: @Rottifanboy15 everyone knows that lol
Rottifanboy15: yeah thats why its good
y0unghercules: Anyone know what is being built here?
PapaDukie: what is ffmpeg
joker2k999: the tower of babel...
shtaken6939: @Rottifanboy15 bro can you share ur git?
davidsit_site: qira. debugger
dorkmo: immortal murder machine
kubaaa6: What you think of terry davis? @georgehotz
grizvok: @Rottifanboy15 you play sc2?
Rottifanboy15: @shtaken6939 most of my projects are private
y0unghercules: what part of this debugger?
Quad___lol: @PapaDukie man this is a stream for programmers...when you dont know, you just ask your best friend
Rottifanboy15: @grizvok yeah i do
blizz191: @PapaDukie ffmpeg is a huge audio/vid library
grizvok: @Rottifanboy15 nice nice.
shtaken6939: @Rottifanboy15 noooooo
JustAnEdtior: u know, i dont understand anything thats happening but ur keyboard sounds nice :D
joker2k999: lol
shtaken6939: @JustAnEdtior sleep with it man
dorkmo: " "
kubaaa6: What you think of terry davis? @georgehotz
alluxua: Same here. I donot understand either
hAhamza: awk that shit
davidsit_site: I just heard you quote David beazley
y0unghercules: command
PapaDukie: @blizz191 is it a library in the same way react is a library
y0unghercules: If you used Temple OS you woudltn need to make QIRA
Quad___lol: templeOS is the best OS... RIP Tery
y0unghercules: Temple OS is the only way out of the simulation
Quad___lol: ((they)) got him
StopitDonk: PogChamp Python to the RESCUE
blizz191: Idk react libraries but ffmpeg is pretty low level stuff so im guessing not
blizz191: RIP terry i agree tho
Flowsyn: hey guys, what program is he working on?
karelomab: George has new hair!!!!
y0unghercules: In what cases would QIRA be used in
Quad___lol: but who is gonna continue with templeOS development :(
y0unghercules: like process crashes?
davidsit_site: You?
blizz191: @Quad___lol the next person god calls
dev12341: @quad___lol the cia :(
z0di4ckx: Python is the best.
Hamled2: the jankiest macro system I've ever seen...
Quad___lol: @blizz191 right :( talking to god on 64 cores is my favorite thing :(
y0unghercules: lol
Quad___lol: @dev12341 should have run them over as he said
Hamled2: Couldn't that have been done with a map at runtime anyways @georgehotz
karelomab: 1m209.com
karelomab: 1m2019.com
y0unghercules: what would the advantage of QIRA be over strace
davidsit_site: step backwards
fa_k: /g/ wannabes in chat
jamesred2313: Why is the screen black
ziggyzergling: _ is private?
Quad___lol: @jamesred2313 screen is compiling
joker2k999: thx
davidsit_site: @ziggyzergling nothing in python is.....just convention/respect /not wanting to fuck shit up
alluxua: Geohot, donot code too late. Sweet dreams ! Bye, guys
funkacrylic: I just hosed my AirPods I the wash F
blizz191: F
hardtarget4: mine went through the washer once, they started working again as soon as they dried out
ziggyzergling: @davidsit_site I see :)
z0di4ckx: Cool
moonify: Hello chat, Are you already following George on Instagram?
aamiiiiii: Oh yes I very clearly see that and know exactly what you are talking about. I also like tracing my peas
imJesse: hows george doin
caylakyazilimci: Hi, ı need donate link
caylakyazilimci: !donate
Niiq: are u using TempleOS? if not you should
hardtarget4: rip terry a davis
abhinavneelam: does anyone understand what he's doing?
davidsit_site: can you measure syscalls in another way
Hamled2: @georgehotz could you run it on a program that you would be able to check the result of the syscall easily?
caylakyazilimci: @hardtarget4 hi, what is qira? ı little know english
Hamled2: rather than just cat
hardtarget4: a 'time traveling' debugger that he wrote years ago when he was at Google
z0di4ckx: pretty cool
aamiiiiii: did he write it for google or was he just working there at the time
imJesse: dude on the front page of reddit is wearing a comma shirt. i cant tell if its comma.ai or not. is there a white version of the comma.ai tshirt?
Hamled2: Oh are you just hijacking the true process to see to what degree you can intercept syscalls with this twilight tracer?
Hamled2: oh is twilight the new tracer you're writing ontop of unicorn
aamiiiiii: @imJesse link the post
aamiiiiii: oh wait
verymelo_: hey cutie @georgehotz
imJesse: https://old.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/b554zo/overcame_my_fear_of_going_places_by_myself_and/
aamiiiiii: its literally the 2nd post
imJesse: ye
imJesse: cant seem to find that version of the shirt on the website
tatted_Schnitzel: what is he doing?>
tatted_Schnitzel: in general and atm
Cube_Is_Life20: hey guys I'm back from my AA meeting
Hamled2: I think he's working on a new tracer for his Qira analysis tool
imJesse: many people in the comments mentioning comma.ai. some shoutouts to george lol
Cube_Is_Life20: George, why python?
tatted_Schnitzel: whats the purpose of this tracer specifically?
Hamled2: I think he's building it because QEMU, the tracer he is currently using, is not building with newer versions
codinggangster: hmm I do not see Pycharm? I wonder how the code is written
esence: don't look at chat, we're dumb
aamiiiiii: ^^^
aamiiiiii: literally noone here knows whats happening other than the surface
ZerkBtw: wha tare you making?
aamiiiiii: ive watched 2 videos on timeless debuggers and still nothing
MoTeMiB: Kappa
aamiiiiii: george you said it best during the 2016 USENIX enigma presentation.. "Get up and stretch. You have been sitting for an hour"
moonify: Such hard to understand
TheFrozenTruth: they should make optimizations to convert list map to list comp internally
imJesse: wish i began learning this shit in my younger teenage years
帥帥雷: Hi georgehotz， i am a student come from Taiwan， i learn so many things from your youtube video.
esence: cute
TheLarry17: what is the point of the program he is making? what will it do?
tatted_Schnitzel: what editor is he using?
esence: he's building a simple Rails app
esence: it's Atom
tatted_Schnitzel: lol
tatted_Schnitzel: is it vi? XD
aamiiiiii: vim
VisionHeavy: its vim, not atom
aamiiiiii: and the thing he is doing is making a debugger
Caene: wooooosh
esence: it's hard to understand what's the tool w/out having any experience working w/ it
aamiiiiii: it is discribed as a timeless debugger so I assumed, currently watching the 2016 USENIX video about you explaining it
JonThomasK: hey
logicunit1: You inspire me to start doing stuff.
JonThomasK: im a nerd for knowing 0x2000197 is mmap sys call
aamiiiiii: wait I think I understand what it is now. He explains what QIRA is essentially here https://youtu.be/eGl6kpSajag?t=385
aamiiiiii: for anyone super confused
帥帥雷: BloodTrail BloodTrail BloodTrail
esence: yup, that's a good samp
esence: stamp
JonThomasK: is that a unicorn import I see? Pog
JonThomasK: those are the parameters being placed into registers preparing for a sycall yes?
IncanSilver: Hey George, huge fan. Keep up the good work. LETS GET THAT INSTA TO THE MOON BABY
小甜甜布蘭你想怎樣: Did you like to drink Mr Muscle?
karelomab: LUL clothes :D
karelomab: thanks mom
IncanSilver: ^
Elyx0: George is a fucking legend
aamiiiiii: @georgehotz Has any company picked up Qira for development or has it just been the group at CMU
jay_al97: what happend?
karelomab: SeemsGood SeemsGood
dorkmo: party1000
aamiiiiii: Will the new CEO of comm allow that? ;)
Elyx0: I had so much fun watching his talk about escaping the matrix
aamiiiiii: ah yeah I havent finished watching that yet, so far so good
Elyx0: It's a very interesting theorical ride indeed
aamiiiiii: @georgehotz did you get a degree at CMU?
TreeJayyy: @georgehotz chair upgrade?
chriws: ar u still needing follows on instagram?
aamiiiiii: how much do 10k followers cost? Will you take that as a donation?;)
karelomab: http://1m2019.com
Ishaan96: Hey george, its my first time actually catching you live!! HI!1
karelomab: oh no, cops!!!
oddtechno: BloodTrail
dorkmo: showlove69
abhinavneelam: why are you such a god programmer?
Hamled2: @georgehotz aren't bots more efficient than real organic Human followers (re: global warming)
haHAAXDDDDDD: no need to buy any bots:P just few minutes and few lines of code and this guy has his own bot
th3_maj0r: "few"
Hamled2: the real trick with bots is making them look real enough to not get kicked off the network haHAAXDDDDDD
akbang47: haHAA
th3_maj0r: writing an instagram bot must be boring as fuck
Hamled2: yeah
haHAAXDDDDDD: @th3_maj0r a joke ":D" he is typing so fast and codes this "too hard for me to understand" code so smoothly
꿀빨러: !keyborad
꿀빨러: !keyboard
SlimEconomy: !uptime
thezilion: !noexistscommands
mudowoster: !commands
aamiiiiii: think he uses an hhkb
chriws: have you ever thought in make bots with machine learning, to do thinks like organic human ? maybe it already exists
grizvok: what the fuck?
Hamled2: @georgehotz currently looking at porting your QEMU patches to work ontop of 3.1.0.... seems like they switched the disassembler to Capstone
karelomab: it does sound like hhkb
MatiGoG: !uptime
dorkmo: george is gone, lets party
th3_maj0r: he is back :(
brown_pig: george, do you know this guy: https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/b554zo/overcame_my_fear_of_going_places_by_myself_and/
dorkmo: DoritosChip
dorkmo: ELF
RomanNYC: Something bugs me about how fast he does things, but then scrolling is slow as hell
Chris_YYM: hey check out the link
Vinndy: yo
joker2k999: lol. i wouldn't do it
aamiiiiii: he has a commai
Chris_YYM: it's just a guy on r/pics with your company shirt on
Vinndy: he's wearing a comma ai tshirt
aamiiiiii: shirt
joker2k999: no comma talk bro's
timetrap2e: would you ever buy a pair of off white x nike shoes??
Chris_YYM: that post has 35k upvotes
geobitz: he likes to say that
Mertonton: is it possible to pee n ppo at the same time?
nozoke: hi buddy how are u doing @georgehotz
Chris_YYM: !merch
Chris_YYM: https://comma.ai/shop/products/comma-ai-hoodie
geobitz: lmao
geobitz: we have qira
geobitz: maybe qira can tell us
Chris_YYM: what is qira
aamiiiiii: I am confused with github (noob). I have a repository with some project that I uploaded from my laptop. How do I now combine those files to current pc that has same stuff except the new folder I added to the repository from my laptop
Chris_YYM: gitignore
thezilion: how many peoples here understand this problems?
Chris_YYM: @aamiiiiii you should try gitignore
joker2k999: what problem?
thezilion: ""problems"""
jesseslco: nice haircut
Chris_YYM: hey @georgehotz if I donate 10 bucks would you sign my steam profile?
Chris_YYM: LUL
thezilion: 1m2019.com
nizero: georgehotz is it true that as a kid you made ur own motorized scooter ride it around and "fix" computers except insetad of fixing them you would break them lol
Elyx0: @thezilion He's not having control over some mapped memory on a child process it seems
nizero: lol
JonThomasK: omg i you the famous guy on instagram?
JonThomasK: are you
joker2k999: he shills fo tea
Chris_YYM: BibleThump
thezilion: how to george keeps the sanity? hm
th3_maj0r: when one day you'll be famous on instagram, will you remember your followers on twich?
Elyx0: Why do you care so much about leeching his popularity
tims_titillating_titties: did we hack reality yet?
thezilion: not needs popularity, only money to get rich.
nizero: georgehotz why u working on qira .. you gonna start writing zerodays again ? win a tesla at pwn2own ?
Hamled2: lol I'm looking at the exact same commit right now @georgehotz
joker2k999: elon musk?
JonThomasK: ^^
litesam: Did you fixed the front-end of the app>
Elyx0: "why is my code not working" ?
Chris_YYM: @georgehotz just out of curiosity, what are some of the hobbies you have besides coding/hacking?
gre255: doesnt /bin/cat take an argument? try cattinng an actual file?
th3_maj0r: @Elyx0 lol
nizero: sorry, i'll follow u on instagram to make up for my error
Protoxus: @chris_yym I'm guessing (hoping), IRL shitposting
th3_maj0r: "the question is how, the question is always how"
Chris_YYM: @Protoxus lol
JonThomasK: subscribe to make up for your error
litesam: Hey, did you fixed the front-end of Qira?
thezilion: @georgehotz will not add butom for donation in your description?
Chris_YYM: guys don't forget to click on that subscribe button especially if you have twitch prime
Elyx0: @th3_maj0r Seems like a good phylosophy too but I like asking why recursively too to get to the bottom, like kids do
radino321: subscribe button hacked my computer UnSane
Chris_YYM: i have 8AM class tomorrow, why am I still watching you?
Elyx0: Can you do a quick recap in a ELI5 style of where you're at now?
Chris_YYM: !uptime
mmtaleghani: happy new hair cut :)
th3_maj0r: @Elyx0 in reality mine was just a quote from "hackers 2"
b_______________________b: @Elyx0 most likely not. These streams seem to be for archive purpose with subtle chat interaction. Stream is most likely not meant to entertain us
Axiom_Infinite: @georgehotz as someone who knows nothing about what you're doing how can i follow along on whats actually going on
ericswenson15: It’s like ninja but useful
ericswenson15: Good job
bc10000: what are you programming, i just joined
joker2k999: when i smoke week yea
Hamled2: @georgehotz you said QEMU is good codebase
joker2k999: *weed
bc10000: the purpose is to go to the 2nd life
dorkmo: sometimes i think about if what im doing will matter in 100 years
ericswenson15: True
Hamled2: @georgehotz but the do_syscall function in linux-user/syscall.c is umm... almost 5,000 lines????
risky_banana: I try not to, because then I overthink what I'm working on and then I don't do anything
ericswenson15: Same
bc10000: nothing we do in this life matters, dont get depressed now
ericswenson15: I think it matters?
ericswenson15: Reproducing matters
aPosterior: to your peepee
bc10000: lol
ericswenson15: Lol
ericswenson15: Exactly
ericswenson15: Idk
ericswenson15: No clue
joker2k999: lol read that one late...
ericswenson15: Are we the first organism to understand how we are organized?
aPosterior: I dont think we understand... we might know about it, but..
ericswenson15: We got it down for the most part
aPosterior: ye, to me that isnt understanding
ericswenson15: Not the variables, but the api yes
ericswenson15: Idk
mmtaleghani: do you usually work at nights? entire night?
ericswenson15: Is that emacs?
ericswenson15: Is it python?
ericswenson15: I found reading to be the only thing that made me better?
ericswenson15: I’m weird but 1 book > 1 month of programming
litesam: Did you update the front-end of the app?
ericswenson15: Good job
ericswenson15: Good idea litesam
ericswenson15: Ok thank you
ericswenson15: Assembly code?
r00tdk: hi
ericswenson15: Lol hi
ericswenson15: I’m a nerd sorry
ericswenson15: Python god
thezilion: wow
ericswenson15: Good job
dorkmo: = is life
ericswenson15: Nice find
litesam: @ericswenson15 is a bot
th3_maj0r: is life
ericswenson15: Ya
ericswenson15: You’re too kind
ericswenson15: I’m a terrible developer too
ericswenson15: Is that actual memory?
litesam: Yup
harmachine: harmachine subscribed at Tier 1.
litesam: Do you have any problem on the front-end?
dorkmo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C_clL6evDxg
paul7115: !uptime
BigGucciGuap: !uptime
BigGucciGuap: oof no nightbot
th3_maj0r: like 6h
BigGucciGuap: not bad
dorkmo: yess
Hamled2: yeah, keep working on this
joker2k999: yea bro.
litesam: is the problem on the front end or back end??
LeVexed: world domination
aMulisha: This was a great stream @georgehotz
Ishaan96: teaching ?
BigGucciGuap: jailbreak my ps4
BigGucciGuap: Kappa
litesam: What are you gonna do after 10,000 instagram followers??
th3_maj0r: reach 990k more
kanogger: wait how long is george coding? I went to sleep to him coding and now i woke up to him coding LUL
LeVexed: that boring huh? Kappa
nanodanger7: good morning :D
th3_maj0r: like 6-7h
kanogger: thank you :D
litesam: What happened to VSCode?
th3_maj0r: ?
LeVexed: question mark
litesam: I saw him using VScode like 2 streams ago, So what happened did he stopped using it?
Mua_987410: 5:41:11
th3_maj0r: I think he just tried it
th3_maj0r: he always code in vim, at least while streaming
dorkmo: the blade years of instagram
aMulisha: are you using MAP_FIXED? @georgehotz
litesam: What is he planning after reaching 10,000 followers??
kanogger: LUL
litesam: Any rant updates?
Sylens__: woah the haircut
BigGucciGuap: im assuming the lag is on my side
th3_maj0r: yes
꿀빨러: What keyboard do you use?
dorkmo: lag goes away when you subscribe
kanogger: i can confirm that
th3_maj0r: lol
BigGucciGuap: lol dont influence twitch to add a new throttle non-subscribers feature
paul7115: how many years do I need to live to get on your level?
th3_maj0r: @꿀빨러 not allowed question pvmanNOO
litesam: @paul7115 I'd say 3 years of consistent studying hours!!
BigGucciGuap: knowing what to search on google Kappa
LeVexed: @th3_maj0r what keyboard do YOU use?
litesam: I think HHkeyboard
th3_maj0r: 5$ keyboard from ebay
Hamled2: goodnight
kanogger: good night george
aMulisha: Laterz
LeVexed: gn
Sylens__: i just got here FeelsBadMan
kanogger: :(
jellyjar: cya
dorkmo: heyguys100
th3_maj0r: nooooo
joker2k999: cool. thanx bro
litesam: Do a stream at 10,000 followers
th3_maj0r: stream moooore
dorkmo: 1m2019